-==破烂熊乐园周年奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊字幕组==-
翻译：TAY rain哆啦 南瓜
校对：otherbreath
-==破烂熊字幕组==-
时间轴：卢 斌
破烂熊字幕组作品
-==http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
新 娘 靠 边 闪
莫扎特5岁时发现了自己的天赋...
Mozart found his calling at age five...
创作出他的第一部小步舞曲
composing his first minuet.
毕加索9岁时
Picasso discovered his talent for painting...
发现了他绘画的才能      哦 谢谢
when he was nine.　　　　 Oh. Thanks.
哦!      老虎伍兹在第二个生日前
Oh!　　　　 Tiger Woods swung his first club...
就创立了自己的第一个俱乐部
well before his second birthday.
我? 我8岁时发现了自己的生活目标
Me? I was eight when I discovered my purpose in life.
我在新泽西凯特区隔壁的圣托马斯大教堂里
I was at the St. Thomas Church next to the Hyatt Regency in Weehawken, New Jersey.
那是我堂姐丽莎的婚礼
It was my cousin Lisa's wedding.
爸爸 让我来
Here, Dad. Let me.
这是妈妈去世后我们第一次参加家庭盛会
It was our first big family event since Mom died...
爸爸心情很低落
and Dad was not in great shape.
爸爸 你能带我去女洗手间吗? 我要尿尿
Daddy, can you take me to the girls' room? I have to go pee.
来吧 泰斯 我带你去
Uh, come on, Tess. Let's go.
该死！哦 真该死！
Shit! Oh, shit!
哦 简尼 抱歉      没关系 我们有丝带
Oh,Janey, I'm sorry.　　　　 It's okay. We have cable.
我该怎么办? 真他妈...
What'll I do? What the f
我到底该怎么办?
The heck am I gonna do?
太感谢你了 宝贝 你拯救了这一天
Thank you so much, sweetie. You saved the day.
简尼 帮我我提着裙摆吧
Janey, get my train.
从那一刻起 我爱上了婚礼
And that was the moment. That's when I fell in love with weddings.
我知道我能帮人们渡过他们最重要的日子
I knew that I had helped someone on the most important day of their life.
我也翘首盼望着自己的婚礼
And I couldn't wait for my own special day.
哦 简 太美了 真适合你
Oh,Jane, that's stunning. It really is. It's the perfect dress.
哦 天啊 你看起来美极了
Oh, my God. You look so beautiful.
真的? 你真这么想?
Really? You really think so?
太迷人了 像是为你量身而做的
It's amazing, like it was made for you.
你的电话 是新娘      太好了
It's for you. It's the bride.　　　　 Oh, great.
谢谢你 嗨 苏珊娜
Thank you. Hi, Suzanne.
简 好了吗?      是 她们刚为裙子卷完边
Jane, is it ready?　　　　 Yeah. They just finished hemming it.
合适吗?      幸好我们身材差不多
It fits?　　　　 I know. Thank God we're the same size.
你要过来了吗?      我马上就送过去
Are you coming now?　　　　 I'm gonna have it over to you in just a minute.
什么别担心 这是你的大日子      谢谢 简
Don't worry about anything. This is your day.　　　　 Thanks,Jane.
来吧 我们离开这儿
Come on. Get that out of here.
你来了！你看起来太美了
There you are! You look great.
谢谢！      快点 我们走
Thanks!　　　　 Okay. Let's go. Come on.
拿着
Oh. Here.
什么?      给你的披肩 化妆品...
What's this?　　　　 I brought you a shawl, Visine, Tylenol...
还有一对耳环      哦
a pair of my earrings.　　　　 Ooh.
整理下头发
About your hair
啥? 那贱女人说把头发梳起来 我梳了
What? The bitch said, "Up." It's up.
好吧 也得搭配这个婚礼啊
Okay. I'll fix it inside.
这些是什么
What's all this stuff?
赶快走
Let's just hurry.
这婚纱难道不美吗? 最棒的是
Aren't the dresses great? The best thing about them is...
你能把它改短再穿一次      太对了
you can shorten them and wear them again.　　　　 Definitely. So true.
笑一个
Give me a smile.
不好意思 右边的
Okay. Excuse me. On the right
我们今天欢聚一堂庆祝
We are gathered here today to celebrate the union...
苏西安和格雷的婚礼
of Suzanne and Greg.
此时此刻我们无比欢乐的
This is a time of great joy...
共同向两位步入婚姻殿堂的
as we honor two people who have come together...
新人致意
to be joined in holy matrimony.
哇哦      不好意思
Oh, wow.　　　　 Sorry.
出租车！
Taxi!
太好了
Great.
谢谢 布鲁克林大街31号
Thanks. 31 Water Street. Brooklyn.
我出300块租你的车一晚
Okay. I will give you $300 flat...
但有个条件      什么
for the whole night on one condition　　　　 Yeah.
你不能看后视镜 否则我就扣钱
You don't look in the rear view mirror or I deduct.
成交?      当然
Deal? Great.　　　　 Yeah.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
嘿 你刚被扣掉20元
Hey. You just cost yourself 20 bucks.
我 我不看了
I No one's looking.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
感谢上帝你总算来了
Thank God you're here. I'm freakin' out.
我忘了的那东西      哦！嗯...
I forgot my thingy.　　　　 Oh! Um
我买了额外的 别担心了
I brought extra. No worries.
太好了      谢谢你
Perfect.　　　　 Thank you.
嗨！      嗨！
Hi!　　　　 Hi!
这裙子很好看 关键是你还能改短以后再穿
Are these dresses great? And the best thing is you could shorten it and wear it again.
的确是
That is definitely so true.
今天我们欢聚一堂来庆祝
We gather here today to join in holy matrimony...
莎莉和普拉喀什的婚礼
Shari Rabinowitz　　　　 And Prakash Maharasti...
这么多朋友的到场莎莉和普拉喀什
known to his friends as "Woody."
让莎莉和普拉喀什非常高兴
Shari and Prakash are so happy that so many of you are here today
你在干什么? 快上车！快点！
What are you doing? Get in the car! Come on!
开车！快！
Go! Go! Go!
坐好啦?      是啊
You in?　　　　 Yeah.
嘿！嘿！你只剩260元可拿了
Hey! Hey! You are down to 260.
你还想继续扣吗?
Are you sure you wanna keep this up?
不！      好的
No!　　　　 Okay, then.
你喜欢哪一个? 黑头发的还是金发的?
Okay. Which one do you want? The brunet or the blond?
我有点喜欢金发的 我不想说谎
I kinda want the blond. I'm not gonna lie.
凯西 真受不了你 你就这么迫不及待吗?
Casey, can't you keep it in your pants for one wedding?
开什么玩笑? 我穿这难看的衣服的唯一原因
Are you kidding? The only reason to wear this monstrous dress...
就是为了让某个喝醉的伴郎用牙齿撕碎它
is so some drunken groomsman can rip it to shreds with his teeth.
几点了? 我还得两个小时左右 所以...
What time is it now? Well, I'm just gonna be about two more hours, so
一会再打给你
I'll call you back.
爱慕是我现在的感觉
#Lovely is the feeling now #
嘿！你穿错鞋了！等一下 鞋配错了
Hey! Wrong shoes! Wait a minute. Wrong shoes.
天啊！你...
Ziggy! What?
温度正在上升
# Temperature's rising now #
哦！天呐！
Oh! Geez!
简 我好饿 你吃东西了吗?
Jane, I'm so hungry. Did you eat anything?
吃了      为了漂亮 我什么都没吃
Oh, yeah.　　　　 It looks gorgeous. I haven't eaten anything.
给你些建议 别空腹喝酒
And let me give you some advice, do not drink Moet on an empty stomach.
会让你晕头转向的
I'll tell ya. Whoa. Fall right off.
你看到我奶奶了吗?
Did you meet my grandma?
是啊 她人真好 我好喜欢她
Yeah. She was great. I really enjoyed her.
我认为她很开心      是啊 非常开心
I think she's having fun.　　　　 Oh, yeah. Lots.
不要停
#Don't stop till you get enough #
继续跟着节奏跳
#Keep on with the force #
不要停      继续 宝贝
#Don't stop till you get enough #　　　　 #Keep on, baby #
不要停下来
#Don't stop till you get enough ##
简 你额头上的是什么?
Jane, what is that thing on your forehead?
我想要在此特别感谢一个女孩
I'd like to take a moment to give a special thankyou to a girl...
她一直伴我左右
who's really gone above and beyond.
她不但主持了我的婚礼还帮我设计请柬
The girl who not only hosted my shower and helped me design the invitation
她陪我准备宴会 去花店挑花还有蛋糕房
She went with me to the caterer, the florist, the wedding cake bakery
八家婚纱店
And to eight bridal stores...
她帮助我重拾自信
where she helped me cling to my selfesteem
陪我试了一套又一套婚纱
As I tried on dress after dress.
所以谢谢你 简！
So thanks,Jane!
谢谢你 简
Thanks,Jane.
好了！准备好了吗?
Okay! Everybody ready?
你还好吗?
Is she all right?
她怎么样了?
慢点 放松 先不要动
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy.Just take it easy.
你不能动 她的伤有点严重
You don't wanna move around too much. Okay. This is a serious injury.
快去给我拿点冰来 你 去拿点酒精
I need you to give me some ice. You, give me a bottle of 100proof liquor...
和可以靠着的东西 快点！
and something she can bite on stat!
好的 她没事
All right. She's fine, folks.
只是撞到头了 大家继续
Just a little bump on the head. Carry on.
你是医生吗?
You a doctor?
不 只是懂一点
No, but Tweedledee and "Tweedledrunk" were bugging me, so
好的 你还记得自己的名字吗?      简
Okay. Do you know your name?　　　　Jane.
简 我是凯文
Jane. I'm Kevin.
恩 谢谢你的帮忙
Hmm. Thank you for helping me.
没关系 站得起来吗?      哦
Sure. Got it?　　　　 Uhhuh.
哦 你还好吗?      我很好
Okay. You're good?　　　　 I'm fine.
那就好
All right.
还是给你找辆出租车吧
Whoa, whoa. Okay. Why don't we get you a cab?
放松点 我们走
All right. Nice and easy. Let's walk.
我对你是
# That I'm irresponsibly mad #
如此狂热
#For you ##
顺便说一句 我喜欢你的丁字裤
I loved your thong, by the way.
我看见你在车上换礼服了
You buzzed past me earlier. I saw you changing gowns.
你一个晚上参加了两个婚礼 是么?
You were in two weddings in one night, weren't you?
很烦人 你不觉得吗?      她们都是我好友
That's a little upsetting, don't you think?　　　　 They're both good friends...
但她们的婚礼在同一晚 我能怎么办?
and their weddings happened to be on the same night, so what was I supposed to do?
不 我不是这意思 你怎么受得了?
Oh, no. That's not the upsetting part. How do you stand it?
我是说 一个还不够糟吗?      我喜欢婚礼
I mean, isn't one wedding bad enough?　　　　 I love weddings. I always have.
是吗?      是啊
Really?　　　　 Yeah.
哪一部分 不情愿的结合
Which part, the forced merriment,
糟糕的音乐还是难吃的食物?
horrible music or bad food?
事实上 是遇上你这样的人
Actually, it's meeting upbeat people like yourself.
爱要有耐心 爱是仁慈的 爱意味着失去理智
Love is patient. Love is kind. Love means slowly losing your mind.
你是干什么的来着?      我是一个作家
What is it you do again?　　　　 I'm a writer.
谁信你
Right.
我到了      我来付
This is my building.　　　　 I got it.
不 我来付      你确定?
No. I got it.　　　　 Sure?
对
Yeah.
140元 你知道自己都做了什么
All right, sweetie. A hundred and forty. You know what you did.
嘿！不 等一下 你要送他回去
Hey! What's No. He's gonna be right back. Hold on.
你不认为这一系列的典礼
Don't you think it's a whole lot of ritual for something that
面对现实吧 只是一半一半的几率
Let's face it It's got about a 5050 shot of making it out of the gate.
真新鲜 一个不相信婚姻的男人
How very refreshing. A man who doesn't believe in marriage.
我只是想说婚姻很伪善
I'm just trying to point out the hypocrisy of the spectacle.
你好高尚啊 你是不是还会
That's so noble of you. Do you also go around...
告诉小孩子们圣诞老人其实不存在?
telling small children that Santa Claus doesn't exist?
因为总有人要揭穿这个谎言
'Cause someone needs to blow that shit wide open.
所以你相信婚姻 却不相信圣诞老人
So you admit that believing in marriage is kind of like believing in Santa Claus.
不 我...
No. I
我不知道我为什么和一个陌生人讨论这个
I don't know why I'm arguing this with a perfect stranger.
但是 婚姻像其他珍贵的事情一样很难得到
But, yes, marriage, like everything good and important, isn't easy.
圣诞老人是另一回事 一直都是
Cynicism, on the other hand, always is.
很高兴遇见你 再见
It was very interesting meeting you.　　　　 Bye.
拜
Yeah.
下周末你还要参加很多婚礼吗?
You gonna be in more weddings next weekend?
我必须去      你参加过多少婚礼?
I have to go.　　　　 How many have you been in, by the way?
像是舞会那种      晚安
Just, like, ballpark.　　　　 Good night.
嘿！你能...      什么?
Hey, you know what? Could you　　　　 Yeah?
没事了      哦
Forget it.　　　　 Yup.
周六 凯恩的婚礼
周六 戴维的婚礼
好的
Okay.
死亡 毁灭 婚礼版
Death. Destruction. Wedding vows. Yea.
让我好好看看
Come to mama.
哦
Oh.
那晚有人早退 你看到了吗?
Jeter hit a walkoff in the ninth. Did you see it?
哦 没有 我周六晚上去工作了 记得吗?
Uh, no. I work Saturday nights, remember?
为了那幸福的一对      是的
Here. From the happy couple.　　　　 Oh, that's right.
你跑去吃椰子蛋糕 看幻灯片了
You were eating coconut cake and doing the Electric Slide.
婚礼怎样?      哦 我看看
So how'd it go?　　　　 Oh, let's see.
新郎看到四散的玫瑰花瓣中向他走来的新娘
The bride wore a gown that sparkled like the groom's eyes...
眼睛就像新娘的礼服一样光彩照人
as he saw her approaching through a shower of rose petals.
你没和新娘上床?
And you're not getting laid?
结婚誓言是以承诺为准则的
Commitments is the gold standard of wedding announcements.
全世界女孩都迫不及待想看周日的婚礼版
Every girl on the planet rips open that page, first thing Sunday.
新娘们为了这个不惜一切代价
Brides kill to get in there.
你到底知不知道能得到多少好处?
Do you have any idea what you can be doin'?
对一个马上就要结婚的女人?      对
You mean to women who are about to get married?　　　　 Yeah.
她们不会给你打电话 不会打扰你
They won't call you. They won't bother you.
甚至会假装没见过你 机会难得啊
They will pretend they never even met you. You can't beat that.
好吧 很快就不那么重要了
Well, it's not gonna matter much longer anyway.
你会在这本子上找到我的婚礼
You're looking at my ticket out of the taffeta ghetto.
做你的白日梦吧
Keep on dreaming.
快走开     好吧
Uh, go away.　　　　 Yes. Okay.
怎么了? 我才不会穿伴娘服来公司
What? I wasn't gonna come to work in my bridesmaid dress.
今天穿得挺高雅的啊
Twoday walk of shame outfit. Elegant.
昨天晚上你干嘛去了?
What happened to you the other night?
你根本就是人间蒸发了
You were barely there, and then you disappeared.
你遇见什么人了?      得了 没有
You meet someone?　　　　 Come on. No.
哦 荒谬的问题
Oh. Ridiculous question.
吉娜 早上好
Good morning, Gina.
你看到我的记事本了吗?      没有
You haven't seen my Filofax anywhere, have you?　　　　 No.
好的 我自己去找找看
No. Okay. I'll go look for it.
你给乔治准备好那些文件了吗?      没有
Did you get those catalog pages in for George?　　　　 No.
别担心 我去准备
Okay. No worries. I'll get them from production.
干得好 让她知道谁是老板
Attagirl. Show her who's boss.
我不是她的老板      你是老板的助手
I'm not her boss.　　　　 You're the boss's assistant.
如果你不滥用权力 这工作还有什么意思?
Same diff. What's the good of your job if you can't abuse the power?
凯西 去算账本吧      你现在倒很专横
Casey, go to Accounting.　　　　 Now you're bossy.
见鬼 我到底放哪了?
Where the hell did I put that thing?
这是个能上头版的构想
That is a great idea for the front page of the section.
哦 道尔 这是你第几次这么说了?
Oh, come on, Doyle. How many times have I heard this from you?
莫林 说真的 这是个很棒的构想
I'm telling you, Maureen. It's a great idea.
真的吗?
Really?
跟你上个构想一样好?
As great as your last great idea,
曝光漫天要价的婚礼蛋糕房?
an expose on pricefixing at wedding bakeries?
是啊！它们宰人啊 一点面粉就要那么多钱
Yes! Yes! They're ripping people off. Flour costs pennies per ounce.
80％的利润 太无耻了
That's an 8000/0 markup. It's outrageous.
的确是 但是没人在意
Yes, it is. Also, no one cares.
那上次我想写的缎带工厂剥削工人的事呢?
What about the piece I wanted to do on the exploitation of workers in lace factories?
那可是杀人啊      行了
That is a killer piece.　　　　 Oh, right.
人们可真想看这样的时尚版块啊
That's what people really wanna read about in the Style section.
凯文 这个板块是我们赚钱的主力军
Kevin, this section practically pays for the entire paper.
我们的广告商要娱乐 有趣的人物故事
Our advertisers want fun, upbeat, colorful humaninterest stories...
跟你的想法相反
opposite their products.
所以我们要帮他们赚钱?
So that's what we're about now? Making money?
出去      好的 听着 这样不对
Get out.　　　　 All right. Listen. That was not right.
我明白 但这次 看 这个女人
I get it. But this one is. Look, this woman...
已经参加了七场婚礼      然后呢?
has been in seven weddings　　　　 So?
光是今年 周六就参加了两场
This year. She was in two on Saturday alone.
不止是关于她
But it won't just be about her.
而是深刻的剖析婚礼产业如何把
It'll be an incisive look at how the wedding industry has transformed something...
重要的典礼转变为税收的流水线
that should be an important rite of passage into nothing more than a corporate revenue stream.
以一种愉快的 鼓舞人心的方式
In a fun, upbeat, you know, cheerful way.
听着 莫林 我在委托事项部都快郁闷死了
Look, Maureen, I am dying back there in Commitments.
再让我写半句关于满天星的报道
If I have to write another sentence about baby's breath,
我一枪崩了自己
I'm gonna shoot myself.
这才是真正的报道 才是我想做的
This is a real story. This is what I wanna do.
我要你继续报道婚礼 这才是你擅长的
I need you covering weddings. That's what you're good at.
也是我想让你做的
And that's what I need you to do.
如果你不让我写这个特别报道 我就辞职
If you don't start giving me feature stories, I'm gonna have to quit.
好吧 一次机会 如果我不喜欢
One chance. If I don't like it,
你就给我回委托事项部
you go back to Commitments for the rest of your life...
面带微笑的工作一辈子
with a big smile on that ridiculously handsome face of yours.
成交
Deal.
你认为他会喜欢这个?      是的
You think he'll like these?　　　　 Yes, I do.
我认为这些照片会让乔治把你拉进他办公室
I think those photos for the fall catalog will cause George to take you into his office...
然后跟你甜蜜的大"战"几百回合
and make sweet love to you for hours and hours.
你这么勤奋工作是因为你不开心
Tell me that crazy crush is the reason you work as hard as you do, 'cause it's upsetting.
我只是爱岗敬业 好吗?
Just like my job. Okay?
不 你希望有一天
No. You just think that one day...
乔治一早醒来发现自己疯狂的爱上了你
George is gonna wake up and realize that he is madly in love with you...
他还会表现出高姿态的爱恋
and he's gonna make some spectacular gesture of love
给简・尼克斯的花
Flowers for Jane Nichols.
是我 谢谢
Yeah. That's me. Thank you.
太好了 我跟男人在床上滚了两天
That's great. I spent two days in bed with a guy,
你却收到了花
and you get flowers.
太好了      没有卡片
Nice.　　　　 There's no note.
简 你不会真认为是你梦中情人送来的吧
Oh,Jane. You don't seriously think they're from your dream guy, do you?
吉娜 你能帮我把花放在我桌上吗?
Gina, can you take these to my desk for me?
没问题      谢谢
Sure. No problem.　　　　 Thank you.
你能不说这个了吗? 没人知道
Would you please stop saying that? Nobody knows.
所有人都知道 除了乔治
Everybody knows,Jane, except George.
是真的
It's true.
卡西 嗨 小家伙 嗨
Gatsby! Hi, buddy. Hi!
过来 卡西 别对着女士流口水
Whoa! Come on, Gatsby. No slobbering on the ladies.
嗨
Hi.
旅行还好吗?      很不错
How was it?　　　　 It was phenomenal. Up and back...
我刚刚度过了最好的10个小时
in 10 hours our best time yet.
这是你第8次上惠特尼山吗?
Isn't that, like, the eighth time you climbed Mount Whitney?
你怎么记得 简?      我也不知道
How do you remember that stuff,Jane?　　　　 I don't know.
我们刚收到这个 你认为怎么样?
So we just got these in. What do you think?
我觉得没有整体感
I think they're too corporate.
我也这么想 它们的感觉不够...
That's what I was thinking. They don't have enough of a feel of being
户外 我是说 没有冒险
Outdoors. Right. I mean, there's no adventure.
或是危机的感觉 这些人太矫揉造作了
There's no danger. Plus, everyone looks way too put together.
是啊 像模特 明白了 我会跟营销部说的
Yeah. Like models. Got it. I will talk to Marketing.
看吧 这就是我为什么留你在身边
See? That's why I keep you around,Jane.
谁能像你一样了解我的心思呢?
I mean, who else could finish my sentences?
你的设计会议在11点
Your design meeting is at 11:00.
然后在92号街有一个福利会议
And the 92nd Street Y called to confirm that you'll be attending their benefit.
你想去吗?      要演讲吗?
You wanna go?　　　　 Do I have to make a speech?
说几句关于生态责任的商务实践活动
Just a few words about ecologically responsible business practices.
一些简单轻松的 你去吗?
Something light and fun. You in?
好的我去 记在日程上
Yeah. Yeah, let's do it. Put it on the calendar...
我得空出一天 对吧?
but I'm probably gonna need to dig up a date for that, huh?
也许吧      至少这是我生活里唯一不用
Yeah. Probably.　　　　 At least that's the one thing in my life...
你来关照的事 对吗?      对
you don't have to take care of for me, right?　　　　 Yeah.
哦 我的老天
Oh, my... God!
别说了      简！
Leave me alone.　　　　 Jane!
什么?      是你把早餐煎饼放我桌上的吗?
Yeah?　　　　 Did you put that breakfast burrito on my desk?
我怕你会饿
I just thought you might be hungry.
这就是我爱你的原因
That's why I love ya.
我也爱你
I love you too.
哦！打得好
Oh! Yeah.
是 你是对的 我需要清醒一下
Yeah. You're right. I needed that.
好了 各位
Okay, everybody.
希望大家今晚都来参加我的订婚晚宴
I hope to see you all at my engagement party tonight.
简 再次感谢你为我安排的一切
And,Jane, thanks again for arranging everything.
不用谢
No problem.
晚宴前你想来我家吗?
Do you wanna come over to my place before the party?
一些出货部的家伙会来...
Some of the guys from Shipping are coming...
他们会带龙舌兰酒和气泡衬垫包装来
and they're bringing tequila and bubble wrap.
不错啊！
Fun!
我不能去 我要去机场接泰斯
I can't. I gotta pick up Tess from the airport.
天啊！你就不能雇人替你去吗?
God! Wouldn't it be great if there was a service that you could hire to do that?
黄色的计程车或是黑轿车...
Like yellow cars or shiny black sedans
我想亲自去接她 她是我妹妹
I want to pick her up. She's my baby sister.
另外 她需要我 所以...
Plus, she needs my help, so
再见啦      谁要跟你再见
See ya.　　　　 Wouldn't wanna be ya.
嗨！
Hi!
耶！
Yea!
嘿！你最近怎么开始旅行了?
Hey! When did you start traveling so lightly?
哦
Oh.
我总在飞机上发生艳遇
I always meet the nicest people on planes.
来吧 9号停车位
Hmm. Come on. Parked in P9.
鲁道夫说他想和我回来纽约 当然
Rudolfo said he wanted to come back to New York with me, of course...
但我告诉他我需要空间 你知道吗?
but I told him that I needed space, you know?
小怪人 鲁道夫！
Spazio, Rudolfo! Spazio.
哦！这里真是小巧可爱 我喜欢这儿
Oh! This is so tiny and cute. I love it.
回家真好
Ah. Feels so good to be home.
离开6个月实在太久了
Six months away feels like forever.
妈妈那时跟我现在一样大
Mom was my age,you know?
差不了几天 是啊
Almost to the day.　　　　 Yeah.
那是场完美的婚礼
It was the perfect wedding
船屋 华丽的乐队 日落下的庆典
The Boathouse, the big band, ceremony at sunset.
除了那套婚纱
Except that dress.
我是说 手工花边和反向的打褶
I mean, the synthetic lace and the inverted box pleats.
我认为那很美
I think it was perfect.
他们真的很相爱
Well, they really did love each other.
这些是什么? 婚礼报道?
What are these? Wedding announcements?
不 只是 我正在...
I'm No. They're just I was
不好意思 我正在回收
Excuse me. I was going to recycle them.
拜托 收集这些干嘛? 当墙纸?
Well, excuse me. Into what? Wallpaper?
是一个人写的
It's just this one guy.
马尔科姆・道尔 我只留着这些 他写的最好
Malcolm Doyle I only keep his. He writes the best ones.
我喜欢这些故事 疯狂的求婚
I just I love the stories The crazy proposals...
订婚
the engagements.
哦 算了 你又不感兴趣 你要在这呆多久?
Yeah. Never mind. It's not really your thing. So, um, how long you stayin'?
一到两周 因为秋季服装秀结束了
Um, a week or two 'cause the fall fashion shows are done,
我没什么工作
so I don't have much work.
说到工作 公司晚上有个聚会
Speaking of work. I am meeting up with some people from the office tonight for a party.
你要来吗?
You wanna come?
实际上 我要和几个米兰来的朋友去喝酒
Actually, I'm having drinks with some friends from Milan.
好了 让我整明白
All right. So, let me get this straight.
你宁可去和意大利模特喝酒
You would rather go have drinks with Italian models...
也不来参加我的完美派对?
than come to my awesome work party?
很奇怪 是吧?      是啊
Weird, huh?　　　　 Yeah.
我尽量去      好 谢谢
But I'll try to make it.　　　　 Well, thanks.
鹅肉在冷冻柜 红牛在冰箱上层
Grey Goose is in the freezer. Red Bull's on top of the 'fridge.
橱柜那有      草莓馅饼！
In the cupboard there are　　　　 Strawberry Pop Tarts.Jinx!
我先说的 我赢了
I said it first. I beat you.
圣马克大街A段      明白了
St. Marks and A.　　　　 You got it.
嗨 吉娜      嗨 乔治
Hi, Gina.　　　　 Hey, George.
不错的派对      感谢到来
Great party.　　　　 Thanks for comin'.
你送了他们高脚杯和一瓶克里斯通(酒名)
You got them champagne glasses and a bottle of Cristal.
她会相信那是我送的吗?
All right. Any way she's gonna believe that it actually came from me?
可能吧 我把它包装得像被车碾过一样
Maybe. I wrapped it like a car ran over it.
想得真周到
Nice. Nice touch.
我去吧台点些饮料
Ah, look. I'm gonna go to the bar, get a couple of drinks.
你们需要什么吗?
You guys need anything. A little liquid courage?
也许来点醒酒的饮料?
Maybe some hair of the dog for you?
不用了 谢谢
I'm good. Thanks.
他问你要不要饮料
He asks if you want a drink,
你应该笑着说 伏特加苏打水
you smile and you say, "Vodka soda."
你们小酌几杯 调调情 然后翻云覆雨
If you already have a drink, you down it. Then there's some flirting, some interoffice sex...
接着意外怀孕 婚礼的福音忽然降临
an accidental pregnancy, a shotgun wedding and a life of bliss.
我们还要编排多少遍?
How many times do we have to go over this?
我不想让他认为我没有责任感
I don't want him to think I'm irresponsible.
是啊 男人就爱这个 有责任感的女人
Yeah. That's what guys want, responsible. Mmm!
你错了 乔治欣赏我的本色
You're wrong. George appreciates me for the way I am.
谁会欣赏一个穿着衣服的女人
What good is it being appreciated if no one is naked?
嘿 简 顺便问一下
Hey,Jane. Look. By the way...
你收到我今早留在你办公桌上的东西了吗?
did you get that thing I left on your desk this morning?
我桌子上?      是啊 那样可以吗?
OOn my desk?　　　　 Yeah. Was that okay?
可以吗? 那太好了      哦 好的
Okay? It was great.　　　　 Okay. Good. Good.
因为 你知道 我们以前不是那种关系
'Cause, you know, we haven't really had that kind of relationship before...
所以我要确定一下是否可以这么做
so I just wanted to make sure you were okay with it.
乔治！      容我先离开
George!　　　　 All right. Excuse me.
哦 上帝啊 是他送的花 他送花给我
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. He gave me flowers. He gave me flowers.
行了 这是现实生活 不是梦幻仙境
Okay. Stop it. This is real life. This is not a fantasy.
你现在就去告诉他你的感觉
You have to go over there and tell him how you feel.
机会只有一次 所以...
Okay. It's now or never, so so now.
就是现在 快去！      好的
Now, now. Go. Now!　　　　 Yeah.
简      不好意思
Jane.　　　　 Sorry.
乔治 这是我妹妹泰斯
George, this is my sister, Tess.
这是我的乔治 不！我没那意思
Tess, this is my George No! I didn't mean it like that.
简是我的助手 像我的左右手
Jane is my assistant. Kind of like my right hand.
她真幸运
Lucky her.
是啊
Yeah.
我需要什么她总是帮我办好
It's kind of like whatever I need, she takes care of.
好像我不能没有她一样
As if I don't take enough advantage of her already...
我今早甚至在她桌上留下了干洗的收据
I even dropped my dry cleaning slip off on her desk today.
干洗收据
Your dry cleaning slip.
事情紧急 所以      当然
It was an emergency, so　　　　 Of course.
这可不是开玩笑
Good fluffandfold is no joking matter.
是啊 特别是当我只剩下最后一双袜子
Yeah. Especially when you're down to your last pair of socks.
对
Right.
想去喝一杯吗?      恩
You wanna get a drink?　　　　 Mmhmm.
本来想跟我姐姐去喝的
Came to have a drink with my sister.
简尼?
Janey?
嗨 你好吗?
Hi. How are ya?
花是不是太多了
Were the flowers too much?
你送的      是啊
They're from you.　　　　 Uhhuh.
你送的 一个憎恨婚姻的人
You sent them. The angry marriagehater.
这真是个好消息
Oh, that'sThat's such... good news.
好消息 嘿 你能帮我拿着这个吗?
Good news. Hey, Kev, can you hold this for one sec?
当然可以      谢谢
Uh, sure.　　　　 Thanks.
操他妈的!
Motherf
为什么? 为什么?
Why? Why?
哦
Oh.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
祝贺你们
Congratulations.
50周年 哇 真是...
Fifty. Wow. That's
抱歉 你刚才说什么?
I'm sorry. You were saying.
我刚才问你是否收到了我的花
Uh, I just asked if you'd got my flowers.
还有个东西给你
Oh, and I have something for you.
我想给你
I wanted to give you
给你这个      哦 天啊 感谢上帝
Here you are.　　　　 Oh, my God. Thank God.
你落在了出租车上
Yeah. You left it in the cab.
上面写了今晚有个订婚派对
It was either the engagement party tonight...
还有周四要穿比基尼出席
or Thursday's bikini wax, so I thought that
你看过了?      不 我试着读过
You read it?　　　　 Yeah. Well, no. I tried to read it.
太难 所有笔记都是难懂的小标记和手写体
It was very hard. All your little notes in the little cramped handwriting.
真令人乍舌 你知道 现在有种叫电脑的东西
It's very Unabomber. You know, they do have these Space Age computer date books now...
能帮你做这些      哦 是啊
that take care of everything for you.　　　　 Oh, yes.
但我不需要别人代劳 谢谢你
I don't need to be taken care of. Thank you.
跟我喝一杯吧
Uh, have a drink with me.
好吗?      你知道
Yeah?　　　　 Uh, you know
谢谢你把我的记事本送回来 很感谢
Thank you for bringing back my Filofax. That was very nice.
只喝一杯 不是在瓦胡岛上 来吧 我来请
It's a drink. It's not a week in Oahu. Come on. It'll take the edge off.
就一杯
Come on.Just one drink.
对不起 我今晚真的
I'm sorry. I'm really not gonna be very much...
没那个心情
fun tonight.
明白 完全明白 所以也许我能在周四遇到你
Got it. Totally got it. So maybe I'll bump into you on Thursday.
也许不会 回头见
Maybe not. I'll see you around.
那是谁? 我也想要个这样的
Who was that? And where can I get one?
他还会回来吗?
Is he coming back?
太奇怪了 我永远都不会那样
That's freakin' insane. I could never do that.
是啊     你没吃过?
No, no.　　　　 You didn't eat it?
上帝啊 我甚至没见过 我保证
Oh, my God. I didn't even see it. I promise.
很晚了 你一定累坏了 我们...
It's late. You must be exhausted. Let'sYou wanna
去跳舞吧      什么? 不 乔治 你不想吧
Let's go dancing.　　　　 What? No. I don't George, you don't wanna
是啊 我们跳吧      好啊
Yeah. No. I'll go. Okay.
但是我得提醒你 我跳的很烂      不是吧
Yeah, but I gotta warn you. I'm a terrible dancer.　　　　 Come on.
是真的 事实上我出过很多丑呢
No. It's true. In fact, on several occasions, they've had to call the paramedics.
你想一起来吗?      嗯...
You wanna come too,Jane?　　　　 Um
不了 你们去吧
No, no. You guys go.
好好玩      好的 我们走
Have a good time.　　　　 Okay. Let's go.
快睡觉 简
Go to sleep,Jane.
睡觉吧 凌晨3点了?
Go to sleep. 3:00 a.m.?
有时我独自出门
# Well, sometimes I go out by myself #
透过水气望过去
#And I look across the water #
我想着你做过的所有事情
#And I think of all the things what you're doin'#
在我脑海中幻化成图画
#And in my head I paint a picture #
因为每次我回到家
# 'Cause since I come home #
身心疲惫的时候
# Well, my body's been a mess #
我想念你柔软的头发
#And I miss your tender hair #
和你习惯的穿着方式
#And the way you like to dress #
哦 你要来我家吗
#Oh, won't you come on over #
不要再若即若离
#Stop making a fool out of me #
为什么你不来敲我家的门
# Why don't you come on over, Valerie ##
嗨 泰斯 约会怎么样? 高兴吗? 什么?
Oh, hi, Tess. How was your date? Nice? What?
他一直在说我?
You talked about me the whole time?
别灰心 我是他生命里重要的一部分
Don't feel bad. I'm a really important part of his life.
我们每时每刻都在一起
We spend every hour, every day together.
嗨！还没睡?      嗨
Hey! Still up?　　　　 Hi.
是啊 我在打扫 调理我的气
Yeah. Yeah,just doin' a little bit of cleaning. Harnessing my chi.
简 我度过了
Janey, I had...
最美好的一夜
the best night ever.
哦 对啊！我差点忘了你的约会
Oh, that's right! I totally forgot you went out.
哦！      对你来说很奇怪吗?
Ow!　　　　 Is that weird for you?
奇怪? 怎么会? 他只是我老板 我才不在乎
What? Weird? Why would it be weird? He's my boss. I don't care. Whatever.
哦 太好了 我们明天要一起吃午餐
Okay. Great. 'Cause we're having lunch tomorrow.
太好了
That's so great!
是啊 我也这么想 你没必要这么小题大做
Yeah. I think so too. Except not quite at that decibel.
跟我说说乔治吧
So tell me about George.
哦 好吧
Oh. Well. I
他 厄...
Uh, he, uh
大学辍学了
Well, he dropped out of college...
然后登遍了世界上的每座名山
and then climbed every major peak in the world.
他在30岁以前就脚踏实地的把一个
And then he started Urban Everest from his apartment...
生态商业企业建立成了
and turned it into one of the most ecofriendly philanthropic businesses in the world
世界上的珠穆朗玛峰
all before he was 30.
哇哦      是啊
Wow.　　　　 Yeah.
这只是他的简介
And that's just his resume.
他是个难以置信的老板 每个人都爱他
He is an unbelievable boss. Everybody loves him. Everybody.
他爱他的狗胜过一切
And he loves his dog, Gatsby, more than anyone.
他不吃红肉 这挺好
He doesn't eat red meat, which is kinda cool.
宁愿花所有的时间呆在户外
And he would rather spend all his time outside than anywhere else.
天啊 听起来真不可思议
My God. He sounds amazing.
是的 但是他也有缺点
Yeah. Yeah, but he has flaws. He does.
人无完人嘛
He is flawed.
什么意思?      他讨厌现金
What do you mean?　　　　 Well, he hates cashews...
这很奇怪
which is weird.
有时他还光着脚穿鞋
And sometimes he doesn't wear socks with sneakers.
我觉得很恶心
I just think that's gross.
简 有什么毛病会妨碍我俩的好事吗?
Jane.Jane, those aren't exactly dealbreakers.
好事 什么好事?
Deal. WhWhat deal?
今晚你们之间什么都没发生 是吧?
I mean, nothing happened between the two of you tonight, did it?
是吗?      这个嘛
Did it?　　　　 Well.
哦 我懂了 不错啊
Oh. I got ya. Nice.
恩 很有趣
Mmm. Fun.
听起来真有趣
Sounds fun.
爸爸?      哦 嘿 亲爱的
Dad?　　　　 Oh, hey, sweetie.
你好吗? 你不必...
How are you? Oh, you didn't have to
泰斯 哦...
Tessie! Oh! Oh!
嗨      看看你
Hi.　　　　 Look at you.
爸爸 这地方看起来一点也没变
Oh, Dad. This place looks exactly the same.
这不公平
Now that's not fair.
我弄了个新遮阳棚 做了木匠活 看啊
I got a brandnew awning. I just stripped and revarnished all the woodwork. Look.
新的收音机 数码的      哦
New cash register. Digital.　　　　 Oh.
爸爸 抱歉 我不知道我错过了这么多
Wow, Dad. I'm sorry. I don't know how I missed all these...
值得纪念的进展
remarkable improvements.
给我那个      我们上楼吧
Give me that. Let's go upstairs.
好了
There we go.
爸爸 我们吃这个会不会太小孩子气？
Dad, aren't we a little old for these?
才不会   太好了 我超爱吃这个!
No.　　　　 Good, 'cause I love 'em!
泰斯 你准备在这里待多久?
So, Tess, how long you here for?
一到两周 对吧? 你是这么说的
One to two weeks, right? That's what you said.
啊 事实上得视情况而定
Um, actually, it just depends on how a few things pan out.
什么情况?
What things?
什 什 什么情况?
WhatWhatWhat few things? What's
你好 嗨!      让我猜猜
Hello? Hi!　　　　 Let me guess.
又有男人追她了?
Some new guy is chasing after her?
我不会说是人家"追她"
I wouldn't call it "chasing."
哦 乔治 我愿意      简?
Oh, George. I would love to.　　　　Jane?
什么?      你还好吗?
What?　　　　 You okay?
是的! 哦 是的 我很好 没事
Yeah! Oh, yeah. Great. Fine. Everything's fine.
当然
Of course.
我得停下来
I gotta stop.
凯文・道尔
她会给我打电话的 我保证
She's gonna call me. I guarantee it.
我有办法让女人自己找上门
I got a way of making the ladies reach out to me.
哦是吗 啥办法?
Oh, yeah. How?
哦 上帝啊
Oh, God.
呜! 你好呀
Whoo! Ah. "Yello."
你撕走了我一个星期的日程安排 你疯了?
You ripped a week out of my planner. Are you insane?
做个小实验 看看没有那些安排你要怎么活
It's a little experiment. See how you do without every second of your life mapped out.
顺便说一下 你的生活才疯狂呢
By the way, your life is insane.
你除了工作和帮别人结婚还做什么?
What do you do besides work and help people get married?
知道吗? 我认为这跟你无关
You know what? I don't see how that's any of your business.
这么多婚礼你怎么忙得过来?
How do you afford these weddings?
我是说婚姻俱乐部的礼服 飞机票和酒水?
I mean, the dresses, the airfares, the wine of the month clubs?
嘿 人们喜欢那儿的赠品 我还是俱乐部常客
Hey, people love that gift. And I'm a frequent member.
有时候会给我免费礼物
So sometimes they throw in a free gewurztraminer.
哇 太可悲了 我真为你难过
Wow. That is terribly sad. I'm sorry about that.
啊 瞧 我想补偿你一下
Ah. Well, look. I wanna make it up to you.
好吗? 买个新记事本还是来个约会?
Okay? How about a new date book or maybe just a date?
啊 好 当然 让我记到日程表里
Uh, yeah. Sure. Let me just pencil you in.
可是 嘿! 你已经写下来了
Except, hey! You already did.
今年的每个星期六都是你
Every Saturday for the rest of the year.
知道吗? 您能不能找别人去?
You know what? Can you please, please find someone else to be creepy with?
不能 告诉你 任何时候...
Nope. Tell you what. Anytime you wanna hang out with somebody...
你不想再陪别人进试衣间或去尝蛋糕...
who doesn't need you to take them to a fitting or a caketasting...
或者彩排婚宴 给我打个电话就好
or a coed mojito and burrito rehearsal dinner, just give me a call.
才怪 行了
Yeah. Okay.
哦 上帝呀
Oh, God.
嘿!      嘿!
Hey!　　　　 Hey!
还让抱抱吗?      当然
Are we getting too old for hugs?　　　　 No.
谢谢
Thank you.
他在那呢
There he is.
佩德罗 你好吗?      嘿 你好吗?
Pedro. How's it goin'?　　　　 Hey, what's up?
佩德罗是我的 厄...      我是他弟弟
So Pedro is my, uh　　　　 I'm his little brother.
我参加了青年中心的兄弟项目
From the Big Brother Program at the Y.
哦      佩德罗 泰斯碰巧是简的妹妹
Oh.　　　　 Pedro, Tess happens to be Jane's sister.
哦      你好 佩德罗
Oh.　　　　 Hola, Pedro.
对了 简 我和泰斯...
Yeah. Um, look,Jane, Tess and I...
正要带佩德罗去参加棒球比赛 你想不想来
are gonna take Pedro to his baseball game if you wanna join us.
不行 我有工作要做 我得留在这里
I can't. I've got so much work to do. I should stay here.
你开玩笑吧 简? 瞧 你的上司可是个混蛋
Are you kidding me,Jane? Look, your boss is a jerk anyhow.
不想被炒鱿鱼就一起来吧      好吧
Let's go. I don't wanna have to fire you.　　　　 Okay.
好吗? 好的 走吧
All right? All right. Let's go.
嘿 你好吗?   还好
Hey. How you doin'?　　　　 All right.
我要3杯无糖百事 3份薯条还有...
Let me get three Diet Pepsis, three fries and
辣热狗 你要辣热狗吗?      哦 不
Chili dog. You want a chili dog?　　　　 Uh, no.
除非是没有肉辣酱的豆腐热狗
Not unless it's a tofu dog with meatless chili.
对不起 什么?
I'm sorry. What?
你是素食主义者?      是啊 最近才开始
You're a vegetarian?　　　　 Uhhuh. It's recent.
哦 是吗?      知道吗? 我也吃素
Oh, is it?　　　　 You know, 'cause I'm a vegetarian too.
我曾是严格的素食主义者 但那太难受了
I used to be a vegan, but it was too much of a hassle.
哦 我知道 我是说当素食者也是种挑战
Oh, God. I know. I mean, even being a vegetarian is a challenge.
我是说 每次徒步旅行我都得带自制便当
I mean, every time I go hiking, I have to bring my homemade "to furky jerky."
你徒步旅行吗? 我是说 无意冒犯...
You go hiking? I mean, no offense...
但你看起来不像那种会远足的女孩...
but you hardly seem like the kind of girl that hits the trails
尤其是看你穿的鞋
Especially in those shoes.
猫咪高跟鞋的公关说它们最适合远足了
The best "to furky" is made by publicists in kitten heels.
我明白你那么想的原因 事实上我热爱...
I can see how you would think that, but I actually love...
所有户外运动...
all that outdoorsy type of stuff
你知道 远足 单车 攀岩之类的
You know, hiking and biking and climbing up things.
但说实话
But, to tell you the truth,
自从我的狗死掉之后 我好久没远足了
I haven't been hiking sinceWell, since my dog died.
我和简看着它长大的 它叫托利
See Jane and I had this dog growing up, Tory.
我好好... 爱它哦
I just I loved him.
它过去常跟我一起远足或是攀爬冒险
He would just go on nature hikes and climbing adventures.
我没有一天不想念那条满身跳蚤的家伙
Not a day goes by that I don't think about that bag of fleas.
哦 老托利
Good ol' Tory.
简 你怎么从来没提过托利?
Jane, how come you never mentioned Tory?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许因为我把对"托比"的回忆藏在心底吧
I must have repressed the memory of Toby.
对 它叫"托比"
Yeah. His name was "Toby,"
我小时候口齿不清所以叫它"托利"
but I called him "Tory" because I had a lisp.
口齿不清到能把"比"说成"利"?
A lisp that turned your "B's" to "R's"?
知道吗? 我小时候有口吃
You know what? When I was a kid, I had a stutter.
不会吧!
No way!
没想到我们共同点这么多      我也没想到
We have more things in common than I thought.　　　　 Yeah, me too.
我要去陪佩德罗"打苍蝇"了
I'm gonna go out and shag some flies with Pedro.
哦! 我好羡慕 听起来好有趣哦
Ooh! I'm jealous. It sounds fun.
什么是"打苍蝇"?      你在干什么?
What are "shagging flies"?　　　　 What are you doing?
怎么了?      你讨厌狗 豆腐和户外运动
What?　　　　 You hate dogs and tofu and being outside.
才不 我喜欢游艇 鲜花和晒太阳
No. I like yachts. I like flowers. I like, you know, tanning.
虽然不完全是同类事物...
I mean, it's not exactly the same
你从来就讨厌托比
And you hated Toby.
你恨它 你根本不喜欢动物
You hated him. The only animals you ever cared about are dead ones with sleeves.
你说那些话只因为乔治很...迷人
You're just saying all this stuff because George is so... attractive.
至少有人这么认为      我并不讨厌托比
Or some people think he is.　　　　 I did not hate that dog.
只要它不缠着我
I just hated it when he slobbered on me.
如果我努力的话说不定也会喜欢豆奶和远足
And I could like soy milk and hiking if I tried it. Maybe.
嘿 泰斯 过来好吗 让我见识一下你的臂力
Hey, Tess. What do you say you come out here. Let's see that arm.
哦 有趣 我们现在要打了吗?
Ooh. Fun. Are we gonna shag now?
以前打过吗?      没 我不知道怎么玩
Ever done this before?　　　　 No. I don't know how to do this.
这样      好的 像这样?
Here you go.　　　　 Okay. Like that?
把胳膊放下面 好吗? 胳膊肘朝上
Put this arm down there. All right? Hold that elbow up.
好的      好 就这样
Okay.　　　　 All right. Hold it there.
嗨
Hi.
谢谢      谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
我对你有点儿心动
#I'm in like with you #
"爱你的 乔治"      啊
"Love, George."　　　　 Ah.
但还没爱上你
#Not in love with you quite yet #
乔治   我的理智
George.　　　　 #My heart's beginning to #
哦 太棒了
Oh, that's terrific.
开始被情感左右
#Slightly overrule my head #
哦不 哦不 我的矜持
#Oh, no, oh, no My selfcontrol #
快被你的柔情攻陷
#It won't hold up for very long #
哦不 哦不
#Oh, no, oh, no #
你触及我灵魂      什么时候一起去钓鱼吧
# You touch my soul #　　　　 We should all go fishing together sometime.
那岂不是太棒了?
Wouldn't that be great?
因为我需要一点时间
# 'Cause I might need a moment #
我不想搞砸这一切 谁知道呢
#And I wouldn't wanna spoil it Who knows #
倘若我还没准备好
#If I am ready or not #
只有时间会证明一切
# To date or not #　　　　 #Only time will tell #
谁知道呢
# Who knows #
如果我们准备好
#If we are ready to make this #
坠入爱河
#Something #
谁知道呢
# Who knows #
你知道在手语里 这代表 "我爱你"
You know that in sign language, this means "I love you."
但我还没有沉沦      我也爱你 泰斯
#But I haven't fallen in quite yet #　　　　 I love you too, Tess.
哦不 哦不
#Oh, no, oh, no #
我的矜持
#My selfcontrol #
快被你的柔情攻陷
#It won't hold up for very long #
哦不 哦不
#Oh, no, oh, no #
你触及到我的灵魂深处
# You touch my soul #
我飞蛾扑火般爱上了你
#I can't help falling too fast for you #
谁知道呢      简!
# Who knows #　　　　Jane!
倘若我还没准备好
#If I am ready or not ##
哪条好看点?   这条
Which one sucks less?　　　　 This one.
好 你能再帮我一次吗?      好啊
Good. Maybe, uh, would you mind again?　　　　 Nope.
谢谢      我经常给我爸打领带
Thank you.　　　　 I do it for my dad all the time.
你还好吗? 你好像有点紧张
You okay? You seem a little bit nervous.
不 我很好
Yeah. No. I'm cool.
我看起来怎么样?      很精神
How's it look?　　　　 Great.
好了 嗯      谢谢
Here you go. Mmhmm.　　　　 Thank you.
嫁给我好吗?
哦 嘿 伙计们 伙计们! 停 不是她 不是她
Oh, hey. Guys, guys! Hold it. She's not the one. She's not the one.
嘿 简
Hey.Jane.
对不起 我该先给你打电话 你钱包忘带了
I'm so sorry. I should've called, but you forgot your wallet.
哦 谢谢
Oh. Well, thanks.
对不起 我晚了
Sorry I'm late.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys. Now, now.
简 这是怎么回事?
Jane, what's going on?
过来 宝贝
Come here, boy.
高利 走吧
Golly. Here you go.
哦!      嘿 泰斯
Oh!　　　　 Hey, Tess.
对不起      啊...
Sorry.　　　　 Um
能帮我个忙吗? 请过来坐
Will you do me a favor? Sit down a second.
好的
Okay.
泰斯 我的父母是青梅竹马
So, Tess. My parents met playing hopscotch when they were,
他们8岁就认识了...
like, eight years old...
现在他们已经结婚42年了
and they were married for 42 years.
我这辈子都在等一个女人
And I've been waiting my whole life
希望能像我父母那样
to feel the way my dad felt about my mom.
也许我一直忙于事业...
And maybe I've been too busy trying to make something of myself...
我觉得我...      哦!
but, I think I...　　　　 Oh!
错过了一些机会
missed some of those moments.
但是 泰斯 我第一眼见你...      好的
But, Tess, the second that I saw you...　　　　 Okay.
就知道我们在一起会很快乐
I knew that we could be great together.
所以 呃...
So, um
泰斯 你愿意嫁给我么?
Tess, will you marry me?
是的 我当然愿意
Yes, of course I will.
乔治
George.
等一下 就是说 你要搬回来住?
So, wait. Does this mean that you're moving back here?
是的
Yup.
哇啊 我... 我不知道说什么好
Whoa. Well, I I don't know what to say.
你先是给了简一份工作...
You give Jane a job...
现在又让泰斯回家了
then you get Tessie to move back home.
乔治 你是我的英雄 真的
George, you're my hero. I mean it.
哦 谢谢 你有一对特别出色的女儿
Oh, thank you. You have a couple of pretty great girls here.
等一下 我拿样东西 哪也别去
Wait.Just a second. I wanna get somethin'. Don't go anywhere.
谁不是呢?
Who isn't?
我真高兴咱两今天来见我爸爸
I'm so excited that we did this today.
他那么高兴      泰斯
He's so happy.　　　　 Tess.
爸爸!
Daddy!
你妈妈会想让你穿这个的      爸爸 谢谢!
Your mother would've wanted you to have it.　　　　 Daddy, thank you!
好的
Okay.
谢谢      好的
Thank you.　　　　 Okay.
简 你不会介意的 对吧      不 不介意
Jane, you don't mind, right?　　　　 No. No.
以后你也能穿
You can have it after me.
不用了 这样很好 妈妈会想给你的
No. That's good. It's right. Mom would've wanted that.
是的 妈妈是想这样的      我的乖女儿简
Yeah. Mom would've wanted that.　　　　 That's my Jane.
好吧 那就这样吧
Okay. Yeah. That's right.
这是我妈妈的婚纱
It was my mother's.
是不是棒极了?      是很美
Isn't that amazing?　　　　 That's beautiful.
爸爸 我真不知道该说些什么
Dad, I don't even know what to say.
我一直在想你为什么想见我
Uh, so I'm just trying to figure out why you decided to meet with me.
你一直躲着我 突然之间...
You've been ducking me and then, all of a sudden
我妹妹要结婚了
My little sister's getting married.
先你一步      我烦的不是这个
Ah, before you.　　　　 That's not what I'm upset about.
那是为什么?
Then what are you upset about?
你不了解泰斯 她会把一切交给我来做的
You don't know Tess. She's gonna want me to do everything.
我不仅要当她的伴娘
I'm not gonna just be her maid of honor.
我还要打理一切
I'm gonna be taking care of everything.
那你干嘛不拒绝?      什么?
So why don't you just say, "No"?　　　　 What?
说不
Say, "No."
你以前拒绝过别人么?      当然了
You have said, "No," to people before?　　　　 Yes. Of course.
很多次 各种场合... 其实一次也没有过
Many, many times. In this situation, never. Not once.
但是你想拒绝的
Ah, but you want to say, "No."
那是我妹妹 我不能拒绝
But I can't. It's my sister.
就因为是你妹妹你就不能拒绝...
But you can say, "No." Because it's your sister
好吧 知道我们接下来要干吗? 来做个练习
All right. You know what we're gonna do? We're gonna practice.
好么? 我们来练习说不 你以为我在开玩笑?
All right? We're gonna practice saying, "No." You think I'm kidding?
转过来 我们来玩个游戏 我很幽默的
Turn around. We're gonna play this game. Come on. Humor me.
好吧 简 借我50元
All right.Jane, give me 50 bucks.
不!      简 50元而已 我会还的
No!　　　　Jane, it's 50 bucks. I'll pay you back.
不
No.
简 我需要你...
Jane, I need you...
借给我50元
to give me 50 bucks.
不?
No?
嗯 不赖
Eh, not bad.
我能喝你的酒么?      当然可以
Can I have your drink?　　　　 Sure.
不!
No!
哦 不      刚才做得很好的
Oh, no.　　　　 You were doing so well.
这次太糟了      嗯
That's terrible.　　　　 Mmhmm.
你去定过花了?      去了
So you went by the flower shop and ordered the favors?　　　　 Yup.
啊哈 请帖呢?
What about the invitation mockups?
发了      这太有趣了!
Done.　　　　 This is so much fun!
我有没有告诉你我还请了朱莉当伴娘?
Did I tell you I asked Julie to be one of the bridesmaids?
谁?      堂妹朱莉
Who?　　　　 Cousin Julie. Second cousin twice removed.
那咪咪咋办? 堂妹咪咪?      哦 绝不请她
What about Mimi? Cousin Mimi?　　　　 Oh, no way.
她挺着个大肚子 会破坏美感的
She's so pregnant. It'll just throw off the aesthetics.
对不起 我知道你不喜欢朱莉
I'm sorry. I know you don't love Julie.
谁会喜欢那个小时候她一直叫我...
What's not to love about a woman who asked me if I chaired...
平胸委员会主席的女人?
the Itty Bitty Titty Committee all through my teen years?
别听她的 你胸部也挺大的 虽然晚熟了点
Just don't listen to her. Your boobs came in eventually. They just missed high school.
第三个伴娘我想让你邀请你的朋友...
As for the third bridesmaid, I want you to ask your friend...
那个特粗鲁的      你是说卡西?
that really rude one.　　　　 Casey?
对 对      我家卡西?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.　　　　 My Casey?
她很漂亮 适合穿无带的伴娘裙
She's really pretty. She can pull off the strapless.
我没什么女性朋友  她们都莫名的不喜欢我
I don't have that many girlfriends. For some reason, girls just don't like me.
真不知道为什么
I don't know why.
好吧 我知道为什么 能帮我问问她么?
Okay. Fine. I know why. Will you just ask her?
当然 当然可以
Sure. Of course.
我在想为婚宴做个幻灯片
So I was also thinking we could do a slide show for the rehearsal dinner.
放一些乔治和我的合照 说点我俩的趣事
You know, put pictures of George and I together and say funny things.
好的      你猜怎么着
Okay.　　　　 Oh, and guess what.
那个你特迷恋的作家...
That writer you obsess about...
想在日报上给我们做个专栏
he wants to do a whole Commitments column on us in the Journal.
他给我打的电话 你敢相信么?
He called me. Can you believe it?
这一点 我绝对相信
At this point, I absolutely can.
听着 你的话我考虑了很久 我认为你是对的
Listen, um, I've been thinking a lot about what you said, and I think you're right.
我觉得如果能像父母那样举办婚礼会很特别
I think it would be so special if I did a wedding just like Mom and Dad's.
你是说?      尤其是穿着妈妈的婚纱
Just like?　　　　 You know, especially since I'm wearing Mom's dress.
所以...你看!
So, tada!
船屋?      是啊
The Boathouse?　　　　 Uhhuh.
刚开始我打电话过去
At first, when I called,
他们说18个月内都定满了
they said they had no availability for 18 months.
我第9次打电话的时候
But then the ninth time I called,
他们说有一家取消了预约
they said they had a cancellation.
因为新娘跟新郎的父兄们...
Apparently the bride slept with the groom's father and brother...
姐姐...差不多一家人都上过床
and sister and all these people.
所以 很明显 婚礼告吹 他们都很不快
So, obviously, it got canceled and they were all devastated.
但这也意味着...
But which means...
三周后我就能结婚了
we're getting married in three weeks.
三周?
Three weeks?
是啊 哦 简 我知道你能很快搞定
Uhhuh. Oh,Jane. I know you can pull it together quickly.
我也不想等那么久...
And I didn't wanna wait that long anyway, so
你能不能为我高兴点
Uh, you could be a little excited for me.
我很高兴... 但是
No, I am. I am. It's just
你也想穿着妈妈的婚纱在船屋结婚
It's just that you wanted to get married at The Boathouse in Mom's dress too.
我知道
I know.
我只是... 没想到你会想这么做...
No, I just I didn't know that that's what you wanted...
但如果你想这样 我希望你快乐
but if it is, then I just want you to be happy.
你知道的      太棒了!
You know that.　　　　 Great!
好 我们现在来谈谈重要的事?
Okay. Now can we talk about more important stuff?
我真不喜欢这些台布
Come on. I really don't like the linens,
我们得租些新台布...
and I think we need to rent new ones...
因为它们跟我选的颜色主题不搭配
because they do not go with the color scheme that I picked out.
那个自私的婊子
That selfish whore.
别误会      别误会
Namaste.　　　　 Namaste.
我不敢相信 难以置信
I can't believe it. I cannot believe it.
没有男人不喜欢她 即使是好人乔治
There is no man that won't fall for her. Even a dogooder like George.
男人见到她就像中邪了一样丧失理智
Men just become hypnotized by her voodoo and they lose their minds.
你不能操办你爱的人和你妹妹的婚礼
You can't plan your sister's wedding to the man you love.
太难受了
It's sick.
不怪她 她不知道我对他的感觉
To be fair, she didn't know how I felt about him.
她也不应该知道...他是我上司
And nor should she He's my boss.
我必须忘掉他 别无选择
I'm just gonna have to get over it. I don't really have a choice.
你也没得选择
And neither do you.
她想让你当伴娘
She wants you to be a bridesmaid.
你别害我了
You are shitting me.
认真点
Hello?　　　　 Please.
不 不 我有原则 我绝不会去的
No. No, I won't do it, on principle.
我要坚持原则 不去 别把我算上
I say, "No," on principle. No. You can count me out.
拜托 别让我孤军奋战呀
Please. Please don't leave me alone in this.
求求你了      好吧 好吧
Please, please, please.　　　　 Fine. Fine.
我是为你去的 如果她惹毛我 我让她好看
Because it's you. But if she crosses me, I'm gonna kick her ass.
也让你好看 要是我喝上点酒...
And then I will kick your ass. Then I'm gonna have a couple drinks
又没有标志说 "严禁说话"
There's no sign that says, "No talking."
三周? 不可能完成的
Three weeks? It cannot be done.
对我来说时间不够!      好吧 嗯...
It is not enough time for one of my creations!　　　　 Okay, um...
安东尼 记得我把你介绍给谢克特夫妇么...
Antoine, remember when I brought you the Schecters...
他们定做的是六层心形杰作?
and they commissioned that sixtiered, heartshaped masterpiece?
后来还做了个能吃的礼物塔...
Then, of course, the tower of edible gifts...
放在史夫曼・卡丹诺夫妇的室外婚宴上
for the SchifmanGuardino outdoor fiesta.
你无所不能 咱俩心知肚明
You can do anything, and we both know it.
你会做这个蛋糕的 并且在三周内完成...
You're gonna do the cake, and you're gonna do it in three weeks...
而且还要打折      三周?
and I would like a discount, please.　　　　 Three weeks?
真让我高兴      太棒了
It pleases me.　　　　 Delightful.
我们的蛋糕定上了
We have a cake.
你来这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
嗨 我是马尔科姆・道尔
Hi. I'm Malcolm Doyle.
什么?      我现在才相信这是真的
What?　　　　 Oh, yes. I didn't wanna believe it till you were here.
嗯 这是我未婚夫乔治      嗨 恭喜二位
Um, this is my fiance, George.　　　　 Hi. Congratulations to the both of you.
谢谢
Thank you.
宝贝 我得接个电话 好么?
Oh. Babe, I gotta take this. All right?
好的      如果蛋糕方面有紧急情况...
Okay.　　　　 If there's a cake emergency...
我马上就回来
I'm right over here.
哦 这是简 我姐姐
Oh, and this is Jane, my sister.
她迷恋你的文章
She's obsessed with your stories.
她还偷偷把你的文章保存起来   好的
She keeps them, but pretends she doesn't, but she does.　　　　 Okay.
她是你的头号粉丝
She's your number one fan.
不是古怪的那种
Not in a creepy way though.
好的      你说你的名字是 "凯文"
Right.　　　　 You said your name was "Kevin."
凯文的凯 凯文的文
As in "Kevin."
我用马尔科姆做笔名来躲开疯狂新娘的追击
Well, I use "Malcolm" for the byline so I don't get stalked by crazy brides.
你是怎么认识乔治的?      你是个混蛋
So how did you meet George?　　　　 You're an asshole.
简      怎么? 抱歉 他跟我说他叫 "凯文"
Jane.　　　　 What? I'm sorry. He said his name was "Kevin."
我只是...我只是有点晕了      等等
I'm just I'm a little bit confused.　　　　 Wait.
你们认识?
You guys know each other?
我们都在这个圈子里工作 所以...
Well, we both work the wedding circuit, so
能让我们单独谈下么? 我要...一小会儿...
Can you just give us one second? I'm just gonna over for one second...
跟他谈谈你
talk to talk about you.
安东尼
Antoine.
你骗我
You lied to me.
没有 我说过我是作家
No. I told you I was a writer.
只是没告诉你我写什么
I didn't tell you what I wrote.
但 但是 你写的东西太美了
But But you write the most beautiful things.
你是不是相信真爱和婚姻却假装愤世嫉俗
Do you actually believe in love and marriage and pretend to be a cynic...
还是你愤世嫉俗
or are you a cynic
像我这样相信浪漫的女孩?
who knows how to spin romantic crap for girls like me?
我不明白 但我想是后者吧
I didn't follow that at all. But I think the second one, the spinning crap one.
天呀 我感觉像是发现自己最爱的歌
Oh, my God. I feel like I found out my favorite love song
其实是关于三明治的
was written about a sandwich.
我能跟你讲讲乔治跟我的故事么?
Um, can I steal you away to tell you about George and me?
当然 当然 就是为这个才来的
Of course. Of course. That's why I'm here.
什么? 泰斯不在这
What? Tess is not here.
我是来见你的      为什么?
I'm here to see you.　　　　 Why?
开门吧 我得从亲戚朋友口中了解情况
Come on. I have to talk to all of the friends and family.
就五分钟好么?
It'll take five minutes. Please?
看在乔治和泰斯的份上?
For George and Tess?
好吧
Well, okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
我能进来么?      想问什么就问吧
May I come in?　　　　Just ask me what you wanna ask me.
或者你还想再撒点谎?      我可没撒谎
Or would you prefer to lie some more?　　　　 I didn't lie to you.
我不知道你为什么一直这么说
I don't know why you keep saying that.
我也许是忽略了点细节
I may have left out a couple of things.
别再计较这个了 行吗?
Can we just get this over with?
伴娘是一个奇怪的年轻女子
The maid of honor is a peculiar young woman.
说说你对泰斯旋风般的浪漫故事作何感想
So tell me how you feel about Tess's whirlwind romance.
再高兴不过了 她是我妹妹
I couldn't be happier. She's my kid sister.
我教会她看表 骑车...
I taught her how to tell time, how to ride a bike...
用洗碗机
how to steam flounder in the dishwasher.
可以说是我养大了她...哦 请别用那句话
I mean, I practically raised her Oh, please, don't print that.
我爸爸会难过的
That would kill my father.
等等 那些是什么?
Wait. What are those?
没什么
Nothing.
该不会是...     不!
Are those　　　　 No!
是伴娘礼服?      不关你事
Are they bridesmaid dresses?　　　　 This is none of your business.
哦! 老天呀
Oh! Good God.
怎么? 你还收集了一橱柜 为什么?
What? You kept them all? You have a whole closet full. Why?
我朋友很多 我也喜欢收集它们
I have a lot of friends and I like to keep them.
对 完全说得通...
Right. Well, that makes complete sense...
因为它们很"漂亮"      有几件并不难看
because they're beautiful.　　　　 Some are not that bad.
"不难看"? 我真想见识一下哪件不难看
"Not that bad"? I'd like to see one of them that's not that bad.
好吧
Fine.
呃...不是那件
Um, well Not that one.
这件...这件真的很...
This one This one is really
糟糕 对吧?你想用的是这个词吧
Horrible. Right? Was the word you're looking for.
这是什么颜色? 呕吐物的颜色?
What color is this? Vomit?
不 这是... 这叫橄榄绿 很流行的
No, it's like a It's an "olivey" green. It's very in.
告诉你 穿身上可好看了
I'm telling you, it looks great on.
不 我告诉你 这叫精神摧残...
Uh, no. I'm telling you that this is an instrument of torture...
新娘让你穿是为了衬托她的美
inflicted on you by a bride who wants you to look ugly.
不 吉娜选它是因为大家穿都好看
No.Jenna picked it because it looks good on everybody.
受访者有轻微妄想症 并轻信别人的说辞
Slightly delusional and will believe anything anyone tells her.
那不是真的 我要证明给你看你错了
That is not true and I'm going to show you you are wrong.
看见了吧?
See?
没那么难看 腰带很漂亮的...
It's not so bad. This sash is really very flat
好吧 你是对的 没那么难看
Okay. You are totally right about the dress. It is not that bad.
但是 你瞧瞧这颜色
But, come on. The color? Please.
那是你闪光灯的问题 曝光出来怪怪的...
Well, it's your flash. I think it's blowing it out weird...
如果好好照...好吧 不是多好看
and if it were just a normal Okay, it's not very good.
你看起来像亮闪闪的美人鱼
You kind of look like a shiny mermaid.
我是在夸你 她才不想站在一个高挑美丽...
You should be flattered. She didn't want to stand next to a tall, beautiful woman...
还穿着华丽的女孩身边
and have you actually looking decent.
这还不是最糟的一件
It's really not the worst one.
如果我必须选一件...我会选这一件
If I had to pick one I got a good one.
这是我最喜欢的      哦 我的上帝
This is my favorite.　　　　 Oh, my God.
那是什么鬼玩意儿?      主题婚礼
What the hell is that?　　　　 Theme wedding.
什么主题  "侮辱"? 天呀!
What was the theme, "humiliation"? God!
不 没人会用《飘》作主题
No, people do not have Gone With The Wind weddings.
我参加过三个
I have been to three.
照吧      好
Let's do it.　　　　 All right.
说"茄子"      茄子
Y'all say, "Diddlydee."　　　　 Diddlydee.
哦!
Oh!
我晕了 你还有什么礼服 多给我看点
I feel sick. All right. What else you got? Show me some more.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
你得让我看看和服   拿来
You have to show me Benihana.　　　　 Give it.
# You ain't got the crime 'Cause she ain't got #
#Nothing' on you #
啊!
Aha!
很漂亮 你觉得自己漂亮么?
Very pretty. Do you feel pretty?
人见人爱
Adorable.
每个新娘都喜欢饰品
Every bride loves her accessories.
男人穿裙子 女人穿西装
Men wore dresses. Women wore suits.
哇!
Whoa!
凯文?      哎
Kevin?　　　　 Yup.
哦!
Oh!
啊...
Um
这是什么主题?
What was the theme here?
洛杉矶婚礼
L.A. Wedding.
如果你感受到这火辣的气氛 就快来狂欢
# You gotta party If you're feeling hearty #
她爱得难以自拔
#She's in love now #
还是你想看到
# Would you rather see #
你知道的 耶
# That you know Yeah #
来吧
#Come on #
总共27件礼服 太开玩笑了
Twentyseven dresses. You gotta be kidding me.
我不明白 你...你参加完婚礼
I don't get it. All right. You You do the thing, you have the dress.
就把礼服扔了呗 看那一大橱柜
Just throw it out. That's a huge closet.
住在纽约 不能那样浪费空间
You live in New York. You cannot be eating up space like that.
也许有点可笑 但它们给我带来了美好时光
Strange as it sounds, I've had some really good times in those dresses.
可能有点怪吧      我不相信你的话
Weird as that may be.　　　　 I don't believe you.
他们让我穿的奇怪点我也不介意
I don't care if somebody wants me to wear a funny dress.
那是他们的大日子 不是我的
It's their day, not mine.
上帝保佑你
God bless you.
如果支持他们的婚礼意味着...
And if supporting them when they get married means...
要去爬阿尔卑斯山...
snowshoeing to a mountaintop in the Alps or...
或把泉水汇成湖再放几只天鹅进去...
helping to caulk a fountain for some swans, then
你真这么干过?
You actually did that?
哦 我为了他们两肋插刀
Oh, I'm a really, very good caulker.
她像菜刀
Likes caulk.
好吧 但说真的
All right. But come on. Seriously.
我是说 你花了多少时间为别人做这些?
I mean, how much time do you spend doing this for other people?
你自己呢? 难道你就没有需要?
What aboutWhat about you? You don't have any needs?
不 我没需要 我是神
No, I don't. I'm Jesus.
总有一天...谁知道...但总有一天...
Someday God knows when But someday...
将会是我自己的大日子
it'll be my day.
这些人都会来参加我的婚礼 所以...
And then all those people will be there for me. So
也就是说如果我能...
That is if I ever
对不起
Sorry.
你不明白的
You don't get it.
没关系的 你怎么可能明白?
That's fine. Why would you?
嘿 我需要你的购物清单
Hey. I need your registry list.
我以为你会在楼下等呢
I thought you were gonna wait downstairs.
那是什么?
What is that?
乔治在泰卢拉德(科罗拉多州)谁在这儿?
George is in Telluride. Who's in here?
没人
No one.
我们来大厅谈      泰斯
Let's talk in the hall.　　　　 Tess.
简...
Jane
他想找份兼职做
He was looking for a parttime job.
他...在打扫公寓
He's... cleaning the apartment.
哦 小子     瞧 别让乔治知道
# Oh, boy #　　　　 Look, don't tell George.
这是佩德罗和我的小秘密 好么?
It's Pedro and my little secret, okay?
我不知道自己究竟在做什么
#I don't really know what I'm doing ##
凯文!
Kevin!
那篇关于伴娘的稿子...进展怎么样?
That bridesmaid story what do you have so far?
遇到点瓶颈 我正想办法呢
Uh, it's a little rough. I'm still workin' on it.
我要看      我还没...
I want to see it.　　　　 I'm not even
现在就看 发我邮箱里      我还没完成呢
Right now. Email it.　　　　 It's notI'm not finished with it. It's not done.
你能走开么? 我没请你
Can you go away, please? I did not invite you.
泰斯请我来的
Well, luckily Tess did.
我报道婚礼时得目击所有的环节
When I cover a wedding, I gotta see every aspect.
你知道 你妹妹想要那么得到处买的东西...
You know, your sister wants so many presents from so many stores...
却连登个记也不自己来
that she physically cannot register for them all herself.
她时间紧迫 定婚期太短
She's pressed for time. It's a short engagement.
天呢 另一个?
Good God. Another one?
对你来说 这只是个焙盘
To you, it's just another casserole dish.
这将是泰斯用来做妈最爱的圣诞烤肉的盘子
To Tess, it's the pot she's gonna cook my mother's Christmas roast in.
哦 泰斯会做饭?
Oh, Tess cooks?
好吧 是我做 但泰斯会在场...
All right. Well, I'm gonna cook it. But Tess will be there...
乔治跟她在一起
with George.
而这个不是一般的 "装花的瓶"
And this isn't just another "vahze."
那叫花瓶
Vase.
泰斯会把它拿出来...
This is the "vahze" that Tess will get out...
因为乔治在回家的路上想买些花
when George brings home flowers, just because he felt like it.
明白了 那这个...
I see. And this
是公鸡形状的伞架 让乔治放伞用的
this is the roostershaped umbrella holder that will hold all of George's umbrellas.
好吧 你就使坏吧
Fine. Be a jerk.
我是说这些不仅仅是用具
All I'm saying is that this isn't just stuff.
这些是他们共同生活的见证      不
These are the things that make up a life together.　　　　 No.
这都是些废品 每年盈利70亿的婚礼行业...
This is the useless crap that the 70billiondollarayear wedding industry...
设法让人们认为不这么做就不会得到幸福
has convinced us all that we have to have or we won't be happy.
知道我怎么想?
You know what I think?
我认为你那些统计数字和理论...
I think that all your statistics and theories...
只不过是障眼法
are just a smoke screen.
哦 真的? 为了什么?
Oh, really? For what?
你的小秘密...不管是什么
Your little secretwhatever it is.
也许是你父母离婚了
Your parents got divorced.
你还没找到合适的女孩
You haven't found the right girl.
而且害怕永远也找不到      不错
You're afraid you never will.　　　　 Mmhmm.
而我认为你如此喜欢婚礼...
And I think you love weddings so much...
因为比起自己你更希望关注别人的精彩时刻
because you'd rather focus on other people's Kodak moments than make memories of your own.
不错 知道为什么吗?
You're right. Know why?
因为婚礼能人忘记自己单身的事实
Because weddings are the perfect place to forget about being single.
我觉得你只想要婚礼... 婚礼 而不是婚姻
I think you want a wedding not a marriage, a wedding.
你有毛病吧?
What is your problem?
是不是你老婆在婚礼上离你而去了?
Did you have your own fancy wedding and your wife left you or something?
中奖
Bingo.
什么?
What?
顺便告诉你 她跟我大学室友跑了
With my roommate from college, by the way.
所以我认为你还能加点分
So I think you get an extra bingo for that.
哦 糟糕 凯文...
Oh, shit. Kevin, I'm
对不起 我...我只是胡乱猜测
I'm so sorry. It was just It was a guess.
猜得好
It was a good one.
作为一对自己一无所知的人...
For someone who has no insight whatsoever into herself...
你把我看透了
you nailed me right on the head.
想不想把店里最难看的东西买给泰斯?
Want to find the ugliest stuff in the store and register Tess for it?
开始吧
Let's do it.
哇哦
Wow.
我说了还没写完呢      不 写得很好
I told you I was not done with it yet.　　　　 No, it's good.
我刚才的意思是"哇 写得不赖"
I meant, "Wow, it's actually decent."
我不得不承认 我惊呆了...
I have to admit, I was shocked...
啊 既巧妙又辛辣...
but, uh, it's smart and, uh, biting...
事实上 同时很有娱乐性
and actually entertaining as hell.
谢谢      你真的看透了这个女孩
Well, thank you.　　　　 You really nailed this girl.
我们把它放在周日的头版
We're running it Sunday, front page of the section.
啊 你可是为了这个才忙得上蹿下跳
Um, here is where you jump up and down with gratitude.
哦... 不 不 不 我只是...
Oh No, no, no, no. I just
认为稿子还不完美 我想精益求精
I just don't think it's perfect yet. I really want to get this right.
我们应该再等一周
We should just hold it a week.
等等 你求了几个月...
Wait. You've been begging me for months...
现在却要我给你一周来修改几个标点?
and now you want me to hold the story so you can move some commas around?
不知道 相处后发现她不仅是个永远的伴娘
I don't know. Now that I'm in it, she's more than just this perpetual bridesmaid.
她身上还有些别的东西
You know, I don't know. There's There's a lot more to her than that.
要不是因为我了解你...
Huh. If I didn't know you any better...
我还以为你对她有点动心了
I would say that you'd developed a little crush.
真好笑 瞧 我会改得更好
Very funny. Look, I know I can make it better.
现在就很好      能再给我一周吗? 就一周
It's good the way it is.　　　　 Will you just give me a week? Just a week.
好吧 出去
Fine. Get out.
嗨      嗨 谢谢你这么快赶来
Hi.　　　　 Oh, hey. Thank you for coming on such short notice.
不客气 很高兴能帮上忙
Oh, it's no problem. I'm happy to help.
在菜肴方面我比泰斯有经验 你可以放心
And I have more experience eating than Tess does, so you're in good hands.
按照您的指示 我们把婚宴用餐准备好了
Now, we've planned your wedding dinner to your exact specifications.
简的电话      是泰斯吗？
Jane's phone.　　　　 Tess?
嗨 我是凯文      嗨！文章写得怎么样了
Hey, it's Kevin.　　　　 Hey! How is the article coming?
会是一篇巨作 你会高兴的
Uh, I think it's gonna be a great piece. I think you'll be very happy.
我快等不及了      嘿 知道简在哪吗？
I can't wait.　　　　 Hey, listen. Any chance you know where Jane is?
我最喜欢泰斯的地方是她从来不胡扯
Yeah, you know, the thing that I like about Tess is there's no bullshit.
她敢于展现真正的自我
You know, she's not afraid to be herself.
乔治 关于泰斯我有些话要说
George, about Tess There's something that I want to say.
什么?
What?
我只是为你感到高兴 找到了你一直追寻的
I'm just so happy for you, that you found what you were looking for.
好的 那么你最喜欢...
All right. So what's your favorite part...
婚礼的哪个部分?
of a wedding?
太容易了
Oh, that's easy.
当音乐响起 新娘走了进来...
You know when the music starts and the bride makes her big entrance...
所有的人转身注视着她
and everybody turns to look at her?
那一刻我会看着新郎 他的表情说明了一切
That's when I look at the groom. 'Cause his face says it all.
那就是真爱
You know, the pure love there.
所以我喜欢参加婚礼
That's why I go.
那么在你的婚礼上 当你进入会场时...
Okay. So when you get married and you make your entrance...
我可以看着新郎吗?
I have full permission to look at the groom?
对 看吧 请确认那个可怜的笨蛋还站在那里
Yes. Please do. Please make sure the poor sucker is still standing there.
没开玩笑吧? 谁能娶到你是他的福气
Are you kidding me? Some guy would be lucky to have you.
之前你对着辣茄狼吞虎咽的样子
And the way that you attacked that tomatillo
谁能抵挡得住？
before Who could resist that?
很性感
Very sexy.
道尔?
Doyle?
嗨      嗨
Hey.　　　　 Hey.
你来干什么?
What are you doing here?
你们在挑选婚宴的菜肴？
Are you guys picking out the wedding meal?
泰斯呢?      她在做头发
Where's Tess?　　　　 She's... getting her hair done.
我只是在帮忙
I'm just helping out.
我们正准备去莱茵贝克的古董店选些亚麻布
We're heading up to Rhinebeck to pick out some linens from an antique store.
我们得走了 我和泰斯还要和我父母吃晚餐
Yeah, we really should go, because Tess and I have dinner with my parents.
我和你一起走怎样?      什么? 不行
Well, why don't I just go with you?　　　　 What? No. No. That's okay.
我会按时送你过去 我借了我爸的沃尔沃车
Um, I can get you back on time. I got my dad's Volvo, and that thing books.
好吧 我真的不介意 这很好
All right, look. I really don't mind. It's totally fine.
关于那篇文章我还有几个问题要问
I got a couple more questions to ask you anyway for the article.
我很乐意通过电话或邮件回答
Which I'd be happy to answer, by phone or email.
如果你们不介意 这很有用
If you wouldn't mind, that would be a great help.
我根本不介意 我坚持
I don't mind at all. I insist.
你跟个电灯泡似的
It was like a lightbulb.
在那碗玉米粥旁边跟他调情
The second I saw you mooning at him over polenta.
你当然会心烦
Of course you're upset.
因为你正在帮你妹妹和你爱的人...
You're planning your sister's wedding...
策划婚礼
to the man that you're in love with.
你陷进了一个恐怖的三角恋
You're stuck in this creepy little love triangle...
一直以来 你为了这个婚宴绞尽脑汁
and all the while, you're about one monogrammed party favor away from blowing your brains out.
真是可笑
That is ridiculous.
拜托 不能告诉他      因为你是好心的简
Oh, come on. Course you can't tell him because you're Nice Jane, you're Sweet Jane.
得了吧 你根本不知道自己在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about, okay?
他们是我的老板和我妹妹
He's my boss. She's my sister.
能策划他们的婚礼我都快喜极而泣了
I am thrilled to be planning their wedding tickled even.
就像我参与过的每场婚礼一样
Like I have been for every wedding that I've been a part of.
你根本无法理解 因为你是个...
But you can't understand that because you're
吝啬 邪恶又愤世嫉俗的人
you're mean... and dark and cynical.
朋友 那是你的问题  与我无关
And, well, that's your problem, pal, not mine.
朋友? 朋友?      对
"Pal"? "Pal"?　　　　 Yeah. Uhhuh.
嗨 朋友 这不算坏 你刚才叫我朋友
"Hey, pal. Pal." This is bad. You're calling me "pal."
噢 你能不能给我安静点?
Oh, will you just be quiet?
我懂了 你抓狂了 我毁了你整个下午...
Look, I get it. You're mad. I just ruined the whole afternoon...
不然你就能和那个永不会选择你的人去快活
of you pining over somebody that you'll never, ever have.
住嘴! 你给我住嘴！
Stop it! Just stop.
好吧 能不能开慢点 好让我看清路标?
Okay. Would you slow down just a little bit so I can read this sign?
我看不清了
Okay. My Spidey vision's not working so good.
你可以开慢点吗?      能不能别管我！
Do you think you could slow down just a little bit?　　　　 Would you leave me alone!
说真的 疯狂的女士 车子打滑了 开慢点
Seriously. Crazy Lady, we're gonna hydroplane. Slow down.
拜托 车子没有打滑
Come on. We are not gonna hydroplane.
哇哦!
Whoa!
哇哦! 车子打滑了 车子打滑!
Whoa! We're hydroplaning. We're hydroplaning!
我们要死了! 我们要死了！
We're gonna die! We're gonna die!
别跟我说话
Don't say anything.
有信号吗?      没有
You got anything?　　　　 No.
说了别跟我说话 没什么好说的
I said don't! Nothing.
打扰 你的公用电话坏了
Excuse me. Uh, your pay phone's dead.
好样的 你们像"犯罪现场调查"里的人
Nice work. You're like one of those guys on C.S.I.
我们能用你的电话吗?
Uh, any chance we could use your phone?
来一杯苏格兰 3刻度(度量标准) 不加冰
Could I get a scotch, three fingers, no ice, please?
你在搞什么?      现在很晚了
What are you doing?　　　　 Well, it's late...
我们找不到拖车
we're not getting a tow,
又被困在纽约的东第雷弗伦斯
and we're in East Deliverance, New York.
我要来点喝的
I'm gonna have a drink.
别这样 现在没人能帮我们
Come on. There's nobody you can help right now.
为什么不坐下来放松一下 喝点酒?
Why don't you just sit down, relax, have a drink?
多漫长的一天
It's been a long day.
给你
Here you go.
好
Fine.
只喝一杯!
Just one!
啊!      2006年2月12号
Ah!　　　　 Okay. February 12, 2006.
克勒的婚礼 你写的那篇专栏感动了我
The Keller wedding. You wrote a column that moved me to tears.
那是我看过得最美丽的笔触
It was downright, flatout the most beautiful thing I have ever read.
我不记得了      你怎么会忘记?
Oh I don't remember it.　　　　 How can you not remember that?
我不记得了      怎么可能?
I don't remember it.　　　　 How can you not?
那天是父亲的忌日 他哥哥从阿富汗回到家
It was the anniversary of the father's death. The brother flew home from Afghanistan.
那样的感情是无法造假的
You cannot fake emotion like that.
当然可以
Oh, yes, you can.
一个好的作家能      你没那么好
A good writer can.　　　　 You're not that good.
爽!
Nice!
婚礼里总有一样东西是让你喜欢的
There's gotta be one thing about weddings that you like.
免费酒柜      不是
Open bar.　　　　 No.
好吧
All right.
当新娘走进来的时候 她迈着神圣的步子
So when the bride comes in and she makes her giant, grand entrance
我喜欢回头看看那个可怜的新郎
I like to glance back at the poor bastard getting married.
虽然我觉得他很蠢...
'Cause even though I think he's an idiot...
他居然欣然地成为合法婚姻的奴隶
for willingly entering into the last legal form of slavery...
可他看上去总是异常高兴
he always looks really, really happy.
不知怎么搞的 我...
And, for some reason, I
你干嘛这么看着我?
What the hell are you looking at me like that for?
你是在讽刺我吗?      什么意思？
Are you shitting me right now?　　　　 What?
那是我最爱的部分
That's my favorite part.
老天 我们居然有共同点
Oh, my God. We have something in common.
对 从统计学上说 那是一定的
Yes. Well, statistically that was bound to happen.
你得承认自己是个大傻瓜
Uhhuh. I think you should just admit that you're a big softy.
你那些愤世嫉俗都是装的 让你自己看起来
That this whole cynical thing is just an act so that you can seem...
很受伤 神秘 性感
wounded and mysterious and sexy.
哇哦 哇哦 最后一个词是啥?      什么?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What was that last one?　　　　 What?
你是说性感吗?      什么?
Did you say sexy?　　　　 What?
觉得我很性感?      不是
Do you think I'm sexy?　　　　 No.
你这么想很合情理      我没有
It's okay if you do. You think I'm sexy?　　　　 I don't.
不 你自以为很性感 这得说清楚
No. I think you think you're sexy. That's the point I'm making.
你认为我自认很性感?      没错
You think I think I'm sexy?　　　　 Yes.
好歌      我喜欢这首歌
Great song.　　　　 I love this song.
嘿 孩子 放松一颗...柠檬
# Hey, kids shake it loose a lemon #
让它变成羽毛(歌词全都唱错了)
# Gotta make a feather #
歌词不是这样的      就是这样的
Those are not the words.　　　　 Those are exactly the words.
抱歉 歌词刑警 歌词是什么来着?
Sorry, lyric police. What are the words?
你会听到令人绝倒的音乐
#You're gonna hear a handsome music #
像是海象的声音
# So the walrus sounds #
"海象的声音"?
"Walrus sounds"?
说吧 彭妮逃脱了水泥喷枪的控制
# Say, Penny's no longer in a cement jet #
你把我吓着了
You're scaring me.
哦 但你这娘娘腔
# Ooh, but you're so laced down #
吧啦 吧啦 本尼和喷枪
# Buh, buh, buh, buh Bennie and the Jets #
哦哦 在被风吹过的瀑布下
# Ooh, in the wind and the waterfall #
哦 宝贝 她是个臭婊子
# Oh, baby, she's a "revocaine" #
她有一对电动奶子      奶子?
# She's got electric boobs #　　　　 Boobs?
和海马毛做的鞋子
#And mohair shoes #
你知道我在杂志上读到过
#You know I read it in a magazine #
哦吼
# Ohho #
我爱死这首歌了      本 本 本尼和喷枪
I love this song.　　　　 #BBBBennie and the Jets #
她有一双海马毛做的电动马靴
#She's got electric boots a mohair suit #
你知道我在杂志上读到过
# You know I read it in a magazine #
哦吼
#Ohho #
本 本 本 本尼和喷枪
#BBBBennie and the Jets #
本尼      本尼
# Bennie #　　　　 # Bennie #
# Bennie #　　　　 #Bennie #
本尼      本尼
# Bennie #　　　　 # Bennie #
本尼和喷枪
# Bennie and the Jets #
他们太帅了!
These guys are rockin'!
真酷!
That was cool!
哇哦!
Whoa!
在克勒的婚礼上我像孩子一样号啕大哭
I cried like a baby at the Keller wedding.
嗯...
Mmm.
早啊
Morning, sunshine.
嗨      给你
Hi.　　　　 Here you go.
谢谢      拖车正在路上
Thank you. Mmm.　　　　 Tow truck's on its way.
好
Okay.
我只想让你知道...我以前从来没这么做过
I just want you to know Well, you know, I never do this.
我知道      不 真的 从来没有 从来没有
Oh, I know.　　　　 No, really. Never. I never do this.
我知道 昨晚你不停的唠叨
Really, I know. Last night, you kept saying it, over and over again.
我从没这样做过  我从没这样做过...
"I never do this. I never do this. I never do this.
我从没这样做过  我从...      可以了
I never do this. I never"　　　　 Okay.
我只想让你知道
I just wanted you to know.
不      确实如此  这是真的
No.　　　　 No, I do. It's true.
这是你们点的菜      谢谢
Here's your order.　　　　 Thank you.
还要什么吗?      不 谢谢了
Anything else?　　　　 No, thank you.
嗨! 是唱"本尼和喷枪"的
HHHey! It's "Bennie and the Jets."
那个..."本 本 本 本尼和喷枪"
Re # BBBBennie and the Jets #
"本尼"
#Bennie ##
唱得太棒了      多谢夸奖
You guys Oh. That was awesome.　　　　 Oh, thanks.
好吧 待会见      好
All right. I'll see you later.　　　　 Okay.
噢 上帝 我昨晚唱了"本尼和喷枪" 对吧？
Oh, my God. I sang "Bennie and the Jets" last night, didn't I?
恩 非常响亮
Mmhmm. Very loudly.
不得不说 你有点走调
And, might I say, you were a little pitchy.
抱歉 你说我走调? 那你呢?
I'm sorry. Me? What about you?
你唱的歌狗都不会听      什么?
You hit notes only dogs can hear.　　　　 What?
真的 真得唱高了
Truly. Truly highpitched.
不 至少我没走调 对吧?
No. I was in key, aat least though, right?
老天 你就是那个女孩
My God. You're that girl.
对 我是本尼 他是喷枪
Yeah, I'm Bennie. He's the Jets.
嗨 她就是报上的那个女孩
Hey, it's the girl from the paper.
什么报纸?
What paper?
该死的
Shit.
"永远的伴娘 作者 马尔科姆・道尔"?
"Always, Always, Always a Bridesmaid by Malcolm Doyle"?
这是什么?
What is this?
简
Jane
哦 上帝啊!      让我...
Oh, my God!　　　　 Let me
听我解释      哦 上帝啊
Let me explain.　　　　 Oh, my God.
简
Jane
简!
Jane!
我告诉了编辑不要登的
Look, I told my editor not to run it.
不管如何 没人会看那个板块
Nobody reads that section anyway.
别这样 你能...
Come on. Will you please just
你他妈的搞什么? 我说了再拖一段时间
What the hell happened? You said you were gonna hold it.
你做不了那些决定 我说了算
Well, you don't make those decisions. I do.
天啊 我还没来得及告诉她 我们设计了她
Oh, God. I didn't even get a chance to tell her it was running. She was ambushed.
我把周日报上24寸的版面给了你
Hey, I gave you 24 inches in the Sunday paper.
现在你唯一该对我说的就是 "我爱你"
The only thing you should be saying to me right now is "I love you."
哦! 你怎么能这么对我?      什么?
Oh! How could you let this happen to me?　　　　 What?
如果简是典型乐于助人的伴娘...
"If Jane is the prototypical, accommodating bridesmaid...
那她妹妹泰斯就是那个傲慢且被宠坏的伴娘
"then her sister, Tess, is cast as the overbearing, overindulged bridetobe...
无论何时 只要不顺心
"who at any moment, one worries,
她就开始围着曼哈顿区暴走
might start stomping around Manhattan...
鼻孔喷火 把飞机从天上打下来
breathing fire and swatting planes from the sky."
我不知道那时他正在写一篇关于我的文章
I had no idea he was writing an article about me.
你? 他在纽约时报里把我写成"哥斯拉"!
You? He called me "Bridezilla" in the New York Frickin' Journal!
我发誓要把他撕成碎片 我要把他大卸八块
I could tear him apart, I swear. I could tear him apart limb from limb.
干嘛?      能让简接电话吗？
What?　　　　 Can I speak to Jane, please?
有什么话找我的律师去说吧!
The only person that you're gonna be speaking to is my attorney!
我现在还没有律师 但我保证会有的!
And I don't even have an attorney, but I'm sure gonna get one!
你这个混蛋!
Asshole!
我要离开这
I gotta get outta here.
你最好注意交通安全
Oh, but you better alert Traffic Control...
因为新娘哥斯拉被放出来了!
because Bridezilla's on the loose!
凯文 凯文
Kevin Kevin
凯文 别再给我打电话了!
Kevin, stop calling me!
在你说话之前 能不能保持沉默?
Before you say anything, can you just not say anything?
我不懂
I don't understand.
你指什么?
To what are you referring?
别这样 没什么大不了的
Oh, come on. It's no big deal.
只是一篇头版的文章..
It's just an article... on the front page of the section...
几张你的照片
with a million pictures of you on it.
谁会在意?     简
Who's upset?　　　　 Jane.
听我解释 我不知道他在写什么
Let me just explain. I had no idea what he was writing.
简 这家伙是个混蛋 他利用了你
Jane, the guy was a jerk. Okay? He took advantage of you.
别担心      我知道 只觉得自己早该料到
Don't worry about it.　　　　 I know. I just I feel like I should've seen it coming.
抱歉      别再道歉了 行吗?
I'm so sorry.　　　　 Would you please stop apologizing?
我叫你进来只是想看看你是否还好
The only reason I called you in here was to make sure that you're okay.
哦 好多了
Oh. Well, I've been better.
我正试着不去想它
I'm just trying to get through it.
瞧 我完全不担心 对吧?
Look. I wouldn't worry about it, all right?
不是每个人都会看那个板块 嗯？      对
Does anybody read that section anyhow?　　　　 No.
缝好后 我不会...
So after we hem it, I wouldn't
简 是你吗?     对
Jane, is that you?　　　　 Yep.
我们稍候再说 嗨      嗨
We'll talk about it after. Hi.　　　　 Hi.
你好 苏      你好
Hi, Sue.　　　　 Hi.
听着 关于那篇可耻的文章我想了很久
So, listen. I've been doing a lot of thinking about the article fiasco...
我决定原谅你
and I've decided to forgive you.
恩      你只是太轻信别人了
Mmm.　　　　 You're just very trusting...
这不是你的错      嗯
and it's not your fault, I guess.　　　　 Mmkay.
泰斯 你真是大度
That's very big of you, Tess. Thank you.
等等 你核对名单了吗?
Wait. Are you checking me off your list?
放幻灯片的时候 我要知道你都说些什么
Um, about the slide show, I know exactly what I want you to say.
我写了份草稿 爸爸说你有所有的家庭照片
So I wrote out a script. And Dad says that you have all the family photos.
对      对 我会把乔治的照片也给你
Yep. Mmhmm.　　　　 So I'm gonna send you George's as well.
看这里 就说这些
Um, here. Please say this and only this.
我们可不想再尴尬了      好 我懂了
'Cause we don't want to be embarrassed again.　　　　 Okay. You got it.
来了
Here it is.
站进来       好
Step in.　　　　 Okay.
好了      就这样
Yep.　　　　 There you go.
真漂亮       你得解开后背的纽扣
It's beautiful.　　　　 You might have to unbutton that back.
等一下      好了
One second.　　　　 Okay.
完美至极 觉得如何?
Perfect. So what do you think?
我以为你要穿妈妈的婚纱
I I thought you were wearing Mom's dress.
是她的婚纱 不过是一部分
It is Mom's dress. Well, parts of it.
那件太老气了 所以我们进行了一番裁减
It was just so oldfashioned,you know? So we could just use a few pieces here and there.
部分?      对
Parts?　　　　 Mmhmm. Yeah.
像这里 还有这个花边
Like this, and the lace.
你剪了妈妈的婚纱?
You cut up Mom's wedding dress?
从技术上来说 是玛丽埃拉剪的
Well, technically MaryElla did.
不过别担心 剩下的我们帮你留着
But don't worry. We saved you the rest.
如果你喜欢 可以穿这件
And, I mean, if you want,you can wear this...
只要这个式样还流行
as long as a silhouette's still in fashion.
玛丽埃拉 我觉得下面还得缝一缝
MaryElla, I think just the bottom needs to be hemmed a little bit.
不 不 不
No. No, no, no, no.
不!
No!
好吧 你可以不穿
Okay, fine. You don't have to wear it.
你根本不在乎
God, you don't care.
除了自己之外你谁都不在乎 对吧?
You don't care about anyone but yourself, do you?
我一直为你找借口 因为妈妈去世时你还小
I have made excuses for you because Mom died when you were little.
但你得适可而止了
But enough is enough!
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
你的所作所为我无法挽回
I can't undo what you've just done.
但我不会让你伤害乔治
But I won't let you hurt George.
他觉得了解你 但他了解到的只是你的谎言
He thinks he knows the truth about you, but all he knows are the lies you've told him.
你还叫佩德罗瞒着乔治
You even had Pedro keep a secret from George.
你现在就去告诉他真相!
You tell him the truth right now!
他和你的那些垃圾欧洲男友不一样
He is not one of your Eurotrash boyfriends, Tess.
他是个好人
He is a good person.
你不能把爱情建立在谎言之上
And you cannot start a relationship based on lies.
真的吗 简?
Oh, really,Jane?
你如此了解是因为你那些成功的经验之谈?
And you know this because of all your successful relationships?
如果你不去告诉他真相 那么我去说
You tell him the truth, or I will.
不 你不会 你连只苍蝇都不会伤害
No, you won't. You wouldn't hurt a fly.
更不会伤害我
And you definitely wouldn't hurt me.
我是你妹妹     已经是过去式了
I'm your sister.　　　　 That was yesterday.
今天你只是一个伤了我心
Today you're just some bitch
剪了妈妈婚纱的婊子
who broke my heart and cut up my mother's wedding dress.
反正这件婚纱也不适合你穿
Well, it wouldn't have fit you anyway.
简 你看起来棒极了
Oh,Jane. You look wonderful.
祝贺你
Good for you.
亲爱的 看着妹妹先你一步结婚一定不容易
Oh, honey, it must be so hard to watch your younger sister get married before you.
是的 的确如此
Yes. Yes, it is.
但是想到我还能和别人一夜情
But then I remember that I still get to have hot hate sex with random strangers...
感觉好多了
and I feel so much better.
祝你过得愉快
Enjoy the party.
噢! 你打扮得不错 我没准会对你感兴趣
Whoo! You clean up good. I might even be into you.
好的 文件在"泰斯和乔治"的文件夹里面
Okay. It's on the desktop under "Tess and George."
还好吗?      很好
You okay?　　　　 Yep.
这不是水
That's not water. Okay.
很好
Okay.
嗨
Hi.
简 谢谢你为我们所做的一切 真的很棒
Jane, thank you so much for doing all this. It's great.
不用客气
Sure.
开胃菜?      哦 瞧啊 小热狗
Hors d'oeuvre?　　　　 Yeah. Oh, look. Pigs in a blanket.
来一个 泰斯?      不 我不吃那玩意
Want one, Tess?　　　　 No. I don't eat that stuff,Jane.
对 明白了
Right. That's right. Got it.
我要去放幻灯片了
Well, I'm gonna go do the slide show.
简      什么事?
Jane.　　　　 Mmm?
只要照着我写的说 知道了吗?
You're only gonna say what I wrote, right?
当然 优秀的伴娘听从新娘的吩咐
Of course. The perfect bridesmaid always does what she's asked.
不会临阵退缩了吧?
Not getting cold feet, are you?
那是什么?      和他? 永远不会
What was that?　　　　 With this one? Never.
嗨 各位
Hey, everybody.
也许你们已经知道了...
In case you haven't already read...
我参加过很多的婚礼
I have been to my fair share of weddings.
在此之前...
So, to start things off...
我想大家都该知道泰斯和乔治的真相
I thought you should all know the truth about Tess and George.
泰斯和乔治是完美的一对
"Tess and George are a perfect couple.
不 是天生的一对
"No, a divine couple.
他们的爱宛如神话一般
"A couple whose love is the stuff of myths.
他们是如此的相像
"Their compatibility is so exact...
只能用天作之合来形容
"that it can only be described as having been designed by the gods.
一张照片胜过千言万语...
Since a picture is worth a thousand words...
我把照片做成了幻灯片 大家自己欣赏一番
I put together a slide show so you can all see for yourselves.
从一开始 泰斯和乔治就注定为对方而生
"From the very beginning, Tess and George were destined for each other.
乔治和泰斯都喜欢动物
"George and Tess have always shared a love of God's furry creatures.
他们长大后 他俩在奉献 承诺
"As they grew up, they both shared the same level of dedication and commitment...
教育方面水平相当
"to their education.
很好      还有作为市民的责任感
Nice.　　　　 "And civic responsibility.
共享快乐
#So happy together #
他热衷于国际时事
"He was interested in international affairs.
她也是
"And so was she.
哇哦
Whoa.
今天 泰斯和乔治有着相同的价值观
"And today, Tess and George still share the same values.
我和你 你和我
#Me and you and you and me #
他们的爱建立在深厚的理解基础之上
"Their love is based on a deep understanding...
并且能接受最真实的对方
"and acceptance of who the other person really is.
幸福的生活在一起
#So happy together #
吧啦 吧啦
#Bah, bah, bah, bah #
两个真正的灵魂伴侣
"The love of two true soul mates...
泰斯和乔治
"Tess and George.
这就是天造地设的一对
So here's to the most perfect couple brought together by destiny.
为你感到自豪 我的小妹妹
I'm so proud of you, Baby Sister.
好了 好了
Okay. Okay.
好吧 那真是...
All right. Well, that was
嗯...
Yeah. So, um...
欢乐乔治的"小兄弟"佩德罗...
to keep the merriment going, um, George's "little brother" Pedro...
他有一些话要说
wanted to say a few words.
佩德罗
Pedro.
告诉我你不是素食主义者也没关系
So, safe to say you're not a vegetarian.
乔治 那是很久以前的事了
George, that was taken a really long time ago.
那你为什么还带着订婚戒指?
Why exactly were you wearing your engagement ring then?
谢谢大家
Thank you.
大家都知道 乔治是我的哥哥
As all you know, George is my big brother.
不止这些
But he's more than that.
他是我最好的朋友
He's my best friend.
现在乔治有了泰斯 她真的非常酷
And now George has Tess, who's who's reallyreally, really cool...
因为她帮助我开创自己的清洁事业
'cause she's gonna help me start my own cleaning business.
乔治 泰斯让我别告诉你的
Oh. Tess told me not to tell you, George.
但是我太激动了
But I'm so excited.
现在我只负责打扫乔治的家
So I'm only doing George's place right now.
如果在座的各位需要清洁服务
But if anyone is in the market for a really good cleaning service...
可以到大厅来找我
please see me in the lobby.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
真不错      不 不是这样的 乔治
That's great.　　　　 No, it's it's not. George.
乔治 等等 听我解释
George, wait, please. Let me explain.
怎么了?
So what happened?
他得知道真相      你本可私下告诉他的
He needed to know the truth.　　　　 You could've told him facetoface.
我知道自己的道德指针也有偏差
I mean, I know that my moral compass doesn't exactly point due north...
但如果我说这件事错了 那就真出了问题
but if I say something's wrong, something's wrong.
是你总是告诉我要为自己而战
You're the one who is always telling me to stand up for myself.
没错 但你表现的并非如此
Yeah. But that's not what you did.
你就像是压抑了20年的感情一夜暴发
What you did was unleash 20 years of repressed feelings in one night.
这很有娱乐效果 别误解我的意思
It was entertaining don't get me wrong
如果你做的对 应该感到舒服了不少
but if it was the right thing to do, you'd feel better right now.
现在你觉得好多了吗?
Do you feel better right now?
婚礼取消了 希望你满意了
The wedding's off. I hope you're happy.
哦 上帝 干嘛?
Oh, God. What?
你怎么在这里?
Why are you here?
你不回我电话      你想怎么样?
You wouldn't return my phone calls.　　　　 What do you want?
还要为你的稿子采风吗?
You want another picture for your paper?
简 对不起 相信我
Jane, I'm sorry. Believe me.
得了吧 你利用我达到事业的顶峰
Please. You used me to get ahead in your career.
是男人的话就承认吧 要么就别来烦我
Be a man and admit it. Or Or don't.
别再假装你在乎了
But please, please don't pretend that you give a shit.
让我解释      不 这不重要
Will you just please let me explain?　　　　 No, it doesn't matter.
我已经毁了我的生活 用不着你煽风点火
I just destroyed my life, and I didn't need your help to do it.
好极了
Great! Finally.
我刚才看到了 我认为那很好
I saw what you did in there. And you know what? I thought it was amazing.
我是认为那很疯狂 但你最终做到了 简
Was it absolutely, certifiably nuts? Yes, it was. But you did something,Jane.
第一次 你不再仅仅是一个完美的伴娘
For the first time,you were not just the perfect bridesmaid.
别再说了 我都不知道为什么和你说话
I'm not doing this with you again. I don't even know why I'm standing here talking to you.
听着
You know what? Let me tell you. Look. Come here. Listen to me.
你知道我今晚为什么来吗?
Do you want to know the real reason why I came here tonight?
我知道这对你很难
Because I knew this was gonna be hard for you.
很久以来 我第一次想成为某个人的依靠
And for the first time in a really long time, I wanted to be there for somebody. Yeah.
我做错了 是我的错 我承认
All right. I messed up. I did. I'm sorry.
我会转身就走 立刻消失
And I'm gonna turn around, I'm gonna walk away. I'm gonna vanish.
你再也不会看到我 我保证
You'll never see me again, I promise.
但我想让你知道
But I want you to know that I think you deserve
我觉得你该得到比你现在拥有的更多的东西
I think you deserve more than what you've settled for.
我觉得你值得被珍视
I do. I think you deserve to be taken care of for a change.
我真的这么想
I I believe that.
我忘了给你这个
I forgot to give you this.
是个礼物
It's a gift...
你不必再随身带着那个1987年出厂的古董
so you don't have to carry around that crazy Filofax from 1987.
你可以用这个计划你要做的所有事
This will take care of all the stuff you need to do.
重新开始的工具
Perfect for starting over.
请收下吧  不然我觉得自己真是个混蛋
Okay. Will you take it, please, so I don't feel like such a jerk?
不要让你的心思变得疲倦 困惑
#Don't let your mind get weary and confused #
你的意愿依然 不要尝试
# Your will be still Don't try #
孩子 不要让你的心变得沉重
#Don't let your heart get heavy, child, inside you #
谎言的力量
# There's a strength that lies #
那篇报道反响极佳
The story got a phenomenal response.
看来你得到自己的专栏了
Looks like you got yourself bumped from Commitments.
太好了
That's great.
开心点
Kevin, be happy.
你得到了你想要的 不是吗
You got what you wanted, right?
孩子 不要让你的心变得孤单
#Don't let your soul get lonely, child #
时间会让一切过去
#It's only time it will go by ##
我说的是 你们是姐妹
All I'm saying is you two are sisters.
你们得好好谈谈     但她不想和我谈
You have got to work this out.　　　　 I'm telling you, she doesn't want to talk.
不 她爱你 一切都会好的
No, no. She loves you. Everything is gonna be fine.
只要你...     爸爸
Okay. If you just　　　　 Dad?
她在这里做什么
What the hell is she doing here?
泰斯 这是你们两个人之间的事
Tess, this is between you and her.
跟我无关
I'm out of this.
你看过新款的除草剂吗
You know, Flo, have you seen the new weed whackers we've got out front?
最新款的
The latest model.
我感觉很不好
I feel terrible.
我对所发生的事道歉       道歉?
I'm so sorry for what happened　　　　 Sorry?
你让我在所有熟人前面丢了脸
You humiliated me in front of every single person that I know...
你觉得道个歉就好了
and you think you could just say sorry?
我知道       简 你总是嫉妒我
II know. But　　　　 Jane,you were always jealous of me.
什么?      总是 我的衣服 我的男友
What?　　　　 Always! My clothes! My boyfriends!
住手     你一直等着打垮我的机会
Stop it!　　　　 You've just been waiting for the chance to tear me down.
不是这样的     就是这样!
That's not true.　　　　 Yes, it is!
你拿走了我一生中最重要的东西
And you took the one thing that was finally working out.
这真是太像你了
Oh, please! This is so typical, Tess.
你不负责任 不承认你向乔治撒谎这个事实
You're not taking any responsibility for the fact that you lied to George.
你控制他 放下瓶子
You manipulated him. Put down the bug spray.
放下瓶子
Put down the bug spray, Tess!
你真的爱他吗 还是只是顺便
Did you even love him? Or was it just convenient?
算了吧 简 别长篇大论了
Oh, please,Jane. Get off your high horse.
承认吧 你恨我
Just admit it. You resent me...
因为你总要为我做头发
because you're the one who always had to braid my hair...
做万圣节礼服 帮我买舞会礼服
and make my Halloween outfits and go shopping for my prom dress.
我不恨那些     不 你恨的
No, I have never resented any of that.　　　　 Yes, you have.
你总是认为我的生活很轻松     本来就是
You always thought that my life was so easy.　　　　 It was!
从前是 现在也是 你根本不用担心
It is! You have never had a care in the world.
你漂亮 风趣 有魅力
You're beautiful and fun and charming.
你的人生是完美的     完美  你疯了吗?
Your life is perfect.　　　　 Perfect? Are you crazy?
你根本不了解
You have no idea.
你知道我为什么要回来纽约吗?
You want to know the real reason why I decided to stay in New York?
我失业了
I got fired from my job.
更糟糕的是鲁道夫甩了我
And to top it off, Rudolfo dumped me.
他甩了我
He dumped me.
乔治出现了  他对我很好
And then George came along, and he was nice to me.
他待我很好  知道吗
And he treated me well, you know?
我想成为他心目中的那个人
And I just wanted to be someone that he wanted.
成为配得上他的
I was trying to be someone who deserved him...
受他尊敬的人
someone he could respect.
我想成为你
I was trying to be you.
为什么?
Why?
为什么你想成为我  你就是你
Why would you want to be me when you get to be you?
事情太乱了      我知道
This is a mess.　　　　 I know.
简     妈妈去世后你就一直照顾我
Jane, you've been trying to take care of me ever since Mom died.
我必须照顾你      不 你不必的
I had to.　　　　 No, you didn't have to.
但如果我不照顾你      如果你不照顾我
But But if I don't then　　　　 But if you don't...
你就只是我的姐姐 那才是正常的
then you'll just be my sister, which is what it should be.
也许我小的时候你得照顾我 但现在
Maybe when I was young you needed to help me out. But now?
别再为我操心了
You gotta stop taking care of me...
还有其他人
of everybody.
你好 嗨
Hello? Hi.
好的
Yeah.
没问题
Yeah. It's no problem. No, of course.
我马上来
Yeah, I'll be right there. Okay. Okay, bye.
你看起来真漂亮
You look You look great.
你终于能在下班后出去约会了
So I guess you did need to find me a date for this benefit after all.
是的
I guess so.
乔治  在我们出去之前
George, before we go anywhere,
我想先为昨晚的事道歉
I just want to apologize for last night.
我不该那样做
I shouldn't have done what I did.
你帮了我个忙
Look, you did me a favor.
和一个认识不久的人仓促结婚是我的错
All right, it's not your fault I was about to marry someone I barely knew.
我到底想什么呢
I mean, what the hell was I thinking, right?
不如我们忘了这件事吧     如果你不介意
So what do you say we forget the whole thing?　　　　 Okay. If you're sure.
我没事     我想再请你帮我个忙
I'm sure. Now, I hate to ask you for another favor...
今晚我要打印我的演讲词
but I need to print up my speech for tonight,
但是我找不到文件了
and I cannot find the file.
我来找好了
Oh, yeah. I can get it.
简 谢天谢地我能给你打电话
Jane, I am so thankful that I could call you tonight.
我总能指望你 你从来不拒绝
I can always count on you. You never say no.
我很欣赏
Which I love.
什么?
What?
我只是说
Well, I I just meant
我说错什么了吗?
I'm sorry. Did I Did I say something wrong?
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
乔治 我辞职
George, I quit.
是的
Yeah.
我辞职      你辞职是什么意思
I quit.　　　　 What do you mean, you quit?
我被这个公司和你吸引到这里
When I came here after college, I was blown away by this company and by you.
但却忙得没时间顾及自己的私生活
And I got so caught up in the job that I never bothered to get my own life.
我曾以为离开很容易
I think I got too comfortable to leave.
但我又不得不每天来这里
Then I had to be here every day to see you
因为我疯狂爱上了你
because I was so madly in love with you.
是的 太可怕了
Yeah. Horrible.
真是疯了
Crazy Crazy crush. Crazy.
你会没事的  乔治
But you'll be fine, George.
你会找到代替我的人
You will. You'll get somebody in this position...
在那个职位上不要超过2年 这才是正确的
who will stay for two years max, because that's what's acceptable and appropriate for this
对不起
I I'm sorry. Really sorry.
我不知道 就像...      没关系
I don't know. It just kind of, like, all of a sudden.　　　　 No. It's okay.
我一直想知道那是什么感觉
I've always wanted to know what that would feel like.
那么
And?
我什么也没感觉到
Nothin'. I didn't feel a thing.
真伤人
That hurts.
那再试一次?     好的 可以
MayMaybe we can give it another try. Okay.　　　　 Yeah. Okay.
不 还是没感觉 你呢?
Nope. Not even a blip. You?
说实话 也没有
Mmm. If I'm being honest, not really.
不该是这样的
Yeah. That's not what it's supposed to feel like.
如果是你命中注定的那个
When you're with the person you're meant to be with...
应该是...
it should feel like
什么声音
Wait. What is that?
我要走了
I gotta go.
你认为我们可以请几天病假
How many sick days do you think we can
而不至于惹麻烦?
really take without getting in trouble?
如果连着请四天 就能休息一礼拜 去坎昆玩
If we took four in a row, we could take a whole week off and go down to, like, Cancun.
抱歉 打扰一下
Excuse me. Hello?
你们知道马尔科姆・道尔在哪吗
Do you know where Kev um, Malcolm Malcolm Doyle is?
他在做最后一场婚礼的报道
Yeah. He's covering his last wedding.
你是那篇文章里的女孩 你很出名
HHey. You're the girl from the article. You're famous.
是的
Yeah.
出租车
Taxi?
17号码头
Pier 17.
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
我今晚只带了一套衣服 走吧
Only got one dress tonight, Ziggy. So just go.
不是吧      快开车
Oh, come on! Oh, c Oh.　　　　 Just go!
祝你好运     谢了 斯格
Good luck!　　　　 Thanks, Ziggy.
婚礼在哪里      最里面
Where's the wedding? Okay.　　　　 Straight down to the end.
知道了 非常感谢
Oh, good. Well, I got it. Thank you very much.
不用客气     感激之至
Mmhmm. You're welcome.　　　　 Appreciate it.
嘿 拉回来
Hey, pull it back!
好了
All clear!
你还好吗      很好
Are you all right?　　　　 I'm fine.
你还好吧?     我很好 是的
You okay?　　　　 I'm fine. Really.
都很好
It's all good.
哦 天呐 别！奇怪
Oh, my God. No way! No freaking way!
你是报纸上的那个女孩
You're the girl from the article.
你在这里干什么?
WhatWhat are you doing here?
那个 好吧
Um, well Okay.
长话短说 有个男人
Long story short. There's this guy.
多说点 多说点
Oh! Okay. Tell me more. Tell me more.
凯文?
Kevin?
凯文・道尔?
Kevin Doyle?
哦 天呐
Oh, my God.
他在那里
There he is. There he is.
嘿
Um hi.
你能做到的 说啊
Come on. You can do it. Say it.
我只想告诉你
Uh, I just wanted to say...
你是对的 一直都是
that you were right about me, about all of it.
我只是听不进去 特别是对你说的话
I just didn't want to hear it, especially not from you.
能开个聚光灯吗
Can we get a follow spot?
你在那儿啊
Ah. There you are.
好吧
Um, okay.
凯文 我一生都在等适合我的人
Uh, Kevin, I've been waiting my whole life for the right guy to come along...
然后你出现了
and then you showed up.
你跟我想象中完全不同
And you are nothing like the man I imagined.
你愤世嫉俗
You're cynical...
尖刻  任性
and cranky and impossible.
但事实上和你吵架
But the truth is, fighting with you...
是我经历过的最好的事
is the best thing that's ever happened to me.
我想我可能爱上你了
And I think there's a very good chance that I'm falling in love with you.
就是这样
So... that's it.
这就是我要说的 我走了
That's all I had to say. So... I'll go now.
抱歉
Excuse me. Sorry.
凯文 我...
Kevin, I just really, um
快过来
Get over here.
我想知道这是为何
#I wonder why it is #
我不想和任何人这样争吵
#I don't argue like this #
除了你
# With anyone but you #
我想知道这是为何
#I wonder why it is #
我不会放松警惕 一年后
#I won't let my guard down #
除了你
#For anyone but you ##
告诉我 你觉得这个婚礼特别吗?
So Tell me, what do you think makes this wedding special?
你是谁?     我为报纸写报道
Who are you?　　　　 I write the Commitments column for the Journal.
一会能请你喝一杯吗?     到吧台等着
Maybe I could buy you a drink later.　　　　 It's an open bar.
也许我会请你喝一杯　　　太棒了
Maybe I'll buy you a drink.　　　　 Yes!
你好     谢谢
Hi.　　　　 Thank you.
性感的泰斯
God, look at how hot Tess looks.
她会喜欢我吗? 我大了一岁
Think she'd go for me? I am a year older.
不知道 我会为你说好话的
I don't know. I'll put in the good word for you, big guy. All right?
你好     嘿
Hello.　　　　 Hi.
我是伴娘
Um, I'm the maid of honor.
我和室友住在威廉堡
I, um, live in Williamsburg with a roommate...
现在在设计手袋
and I just started designing my own line of deeply fabulous handbags.
我破产了 不过没事
And I'm completely broke. But that's okay.
我一天只吃一个汉堡
I eat a hamburger a day, and my idea of a pet is a rock.
很高兴认识你     泰斯
Well, it's very nice to meet you.　　　　 Tess.
泰斯 知道了
Tess. Got it.
等会见见新娘吧 她很漂亮
Well, wait until you see the bride. She looks gorgeous.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
一切就绪
Everything's perfect.
尤其是这裙子 把它改短了还能再穿
And this dress the best thing is I can shorten it and wear it again.
太对了
Definitely. So true.
好了
All right.
好了吗?
Okay. Ready?
好了
Yes.
那天我穿上了第28套礼服
That day, I woke up and put on my 28th dress.
我出席了一场没人让我拿花束
I went to a wedding where no one asked me to hold the bouquet...
拿感言稿 提裙摆的婚礼
fold a place card or hold their dress while they peed.
一切都很完美 我都不在意
Everything was perfect. And I didn't care...
因为对我来说最重要的
because right then, the only thing that mattered...
是在走道的那端等我的那个人
was the person waiting for me at the end of the aisle.
用我一直期盼的目光注视着我
And he was looking at me the way I'd always hoped.
这就是你一直期待着的那一刻
So is this moment everything you hoped for?
不
No.
比我期待的好 好太多了
It's more. It's much more.
两位恋人  我们在此集聚一堂
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here today...
见证简・尼克斯和凯文・道尔的婚礼
to join Jane Nichols and Kevin Doyle in holy matrimony.
婚姻让人喜悦
Marriage is a cause for celebration.
事实证明 我说对了一件事
It turns out I was right about one thing.
我知道她们总有一天会为我而聚在一起
I knew they'd all be there for me someday.
我真的明白了爱
#Now I really see Love #
已经降临于我
#Has fallen on me #
哦 你带来多么温和的爱
#Oh, what tender love you bring #
爱情     不是游戏
#Love #　　　　 #No, it's not a game #
已经降临于我
#Has fallen on me #
哦 你带来多么温和的爱
#Oh, what tender love you bring #
现在我宣布你们正式成为夫妻
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
你可以吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
破烂熊字幕组作品
-==http://Www.Ragbear.Com==-
欢 迎 加 入
你那些温柔的爱恋
# What tender love you bring #
我和你坠入爱河
#I fell in love with you #
和你坠入爱河(一切…更多)
#Fell in love with you #
9月的一天(一切…更多)
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came tumbling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降（27个伴娘）
#Love came tumbling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came tumbling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came tumbling down on me #
爱火在心底燃烧
#Love is a burning inside #
我从未感受过的思绪 哦 不
#I've never had this feeling before, no #
我只知道这让我变了个人
#All I know is that it won't let me be myself #
嘿
#Hey #
这是真爱吗
#Is this really love #
哦 也许就是它让我如此雀跃
#Oh, maybe that's the reason I feel so good #
有你在身边
# When you're around #
感觉很幸福 当你在我身边的时候
#Feel so good when you're around #
我为什么记不起
# Why can't I remember #
为你的魅力而倾倒的那天
# The day I melted before your charms #
哦 这就要说到9月的那天
#Oh, was it way back in September #
当你把我搂进你的臂弯
# When you held me in your arms #
现在我知道 你就是我的唯一
#Now that I see that you're the one for me #
一切不再是未知数
#It's no more a mystery #
爱情从天而降
#Love has fallen down on me #
哦 我深深爱上了你
#Ooh, I'm in love with you #
爱情
#Love #
从天而降
#Has fallen on me #
我看到了真爱
#Now I really see Love #
降临
#Has fallen on me #
哦 你那些温柔的爱恋
#Ooh, what tender love you bring #
爱情
#Love #
从天而降
#Has fallen on me #
我不敢相信自己的眼睛
#And I can't believe my eyes #
爱情     9月的一天
#Love #　　　　 #One day in September #
从天而降
#Has fallen on me #
哦 哦 哦 爱情四散开来
#Oh, oh, oh Love came fallin' all around #
我深深爱上了你
#I fell in love with you #
爱上了你
#Fell in love with #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me #
9月的一天
#One day in September #
爱情从天而降
#Love came falling down on me ##